<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Andrew Kraemer's Sunshine Emporium</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
 <updated>2017-03-17T00:15:00-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <author>
   <name>Andrew Kraemer</name>
   <email>kidman007@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>I Would Like to Write a Blog Post but It’s Been Almost Two Years and I Don’t Really Know Where to Start</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/new/blog/2017/03/15/i-dont-know-what-to-write/"/>
   <updated>2017-03-15T20:14:12-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/new/blog/2017/03/15/i-dont-know-what-to-write</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-part-where-i-apologize-for-doing-something-no-one-ever-asked-me-to-do&quot;&gt;The part where I apologize for doing something no one ever asked me to do&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Andrew Kraemer. I live in Madison. I am tall. I am simple. I talk a lot. I use periods where most people would put commas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started a blog on Wordpress a long time ago, and I haven’t added anything to it for a year and a half. The blog was an opportunity for me to explore my enjoyment of language and work on my writing anxiety. For the most part, the blog worked. I think I’m a better writer for it. I struggle a lot less with writer’s block as a result. Looking back on the blog, I’m impressed with the consistency I was able to publish content — despite the limited free time I had when I wrote it. Moving to Madison was a significant turning point in my life, which I failed to capture and share on my blog. That’s okay. I did other things. Change, it turns out, is hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have recently decided to start the blog up again. A friend of mine asked me why I stopped writing. I opened my mouth, then I closed my mouth. I opened my mouth up again and said the words, “Honestly, I don’t really remember.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not a doctor, but I don’t think , “I don’t remember” is a particularly good reason to do or not do anything. So here we are again, a new blog on a new website with new words. The new website is my attempt to get better at some of the backend coding that comes with working on the internet. The words are for me and you. We can share the words like a team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s get back to fun things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-classically-funny-part-at-the-expense-of-a-stranger&quot;&gt;The classically funny part at the expense of a stranger&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first year in Madison I lived with my dear friend, Tony Darling. Tony was an excellent roommate. Tony was my plus one for everything — from jogging to concerts; we even accidentally went to a pyramid scheme presentation together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were scammed as a duo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tony Darling is now in Russia, which is very far away from Madison. I am proud of him, but he needed to be replaced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My new roommate is Kevin Tran. Kevin Tran is from a place called &lt;em&gt;Craigslist&lt;/em&gt;. Kevin Tran and I have a very good relationship. The following is an exhaustive list detailing our relationship:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If we are both in the kitchen cooking something, we make eye contact, and we say, “Hey.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If I am in the living room singing and playing the guitar and Kevin Tran walks by me to go the kitchen, we do not make eye contact, and we do not say, “Hey.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If one of us were to die, the other wouldn’t notice until the smell of the decaying corpse became an issue.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We share the cost of rent.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kevin pays more for rent than I do.
It took some time to learn how to deal with Post Tony Supergoodtimes Depression (PTSD), but now I have Kevin Tran. Kevin Tran is fine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-part-that-focuses-on-a-select-audience&quot;&gt;The part that focuses on a select audience&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far, March has been phenomenal. March has been much better than February. All of February, I felt sick and lethargic, which is unfortunate because February was beautiful. The Germans have a work for this: &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Springtime_lethargy&quot;&gt;Frühjahrsmüdigkeit&lt;/a&gt;, which is a fancy German way of blaming my sickness on the increasing of the temperatures, rather than not allowing myself to rest and recover. Thank you, Germans for this word.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was fortunate to visit my dear friends in both the Twin Cities and Seattle these last few weekends. Seeing my friends brought me an incredible amount of joy. However, it’s more like a joy that is personal and soaked in nostalgia — rather than one that is easily explained to internet at large. I just have this to say:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Thank you my good friends for being excellent&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-part-where-i-suggest-things&quot;&gt;The part where I suggest things&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made sure to optimize Frühjahrsmüdigkeit, by watching several good movies. &lt;em&gt;Captain Fantastic&lt;/em&gt; is one of the best movies I have ever seen. I love everything about this movie. I could argue that it was my favorite of 2016. It’s distilled whimsy and intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also really liked &lt;em&gt;10 Cloverfield Lane&lt;/em&gt;. If you didn’t like &lt;em&gt;Cloverfield&lt;/em&gt;, you should probably watch this anyway. John Goodman kills it in this one. It’s scary in a wonderful way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/2ZqNeGaS08ga03TmmrEVjn&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; playlist for you. It’s called &lt;em&gt;Distilled Friendship&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-part-where-i-thank-you&quot;&gt;The part where I thank you&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s been a really good year and a half. Lots has happened, and I — for once in my life — had to stop myself from writing. Sometimes I’ve been creative and other times I’ve been lazy. Regardless, it’s always nice to share, and I always appreciate you reading. More to come soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andrew&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>I Think I'll Call This One 'Madison'</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2015/08/05/i-think-ill-call-this-one-madison/"/>
   <updated>2015-08-05T18:10:43-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2015/08/05/i-think-ill-call-this-one-madison</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, I made it to Madison.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Often times, when I’m writing a blog post, I’ll write out what’s on my mind in my snazzy notebook. It helps me get my thoughts out fast and dirty. It’s also the notebook I bought so that when I go into coffee shops, like the one I’m in now, people will know that I went to a liberal arts school — or at the very least that I’m a *creative* person. It’s like a Moleskine, but it’s a different brand. That’s how creative I am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though it’s nice signaling to everyone how creative I am, I’ll admit that it’s disappointing when I opened my notebook today and saw that I haven’t written in my *creative* notebook since I was taking notes for my interview at wellbe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— This means at least two things&lt;br /&gt;
1. It has been a full month since I interviewed for the position that I started yesterday&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;del&gt;2. My assumption that it would be easier to write about my transition from Chicago to Madison would be easier once I left Catamaran — now Optum — was wrong. Or maybe it wasn’t wrong because I guess that I’m writing about my move right now, because here I am — in a cafe — writing about writing. Regardless, I thought that it would be easier to write about moving to Madison because I was afraid that someone at work would find out, which — in retrospect — is a ridiculous thing to worry about. I guess I really wanted to avoid an unlikely — but definitely possible — situation where a boss would find out I was looking to move and I got fired before I was able to secure a job in Madison. For instance, I could have posted a blog post about moving to Madison on Twitter and one of the famous people who follow me — like Taylor Swift — could have retweeted it. As a result, a tween (do people still say that?) would show their parent the post out of sympathy for the author (me). That parent would end up being my boss’s boss’s boss, who would see that I was planning on leaving and then fire me. As a result, I would be found dead by the side of I-94 between Milwaukee and Madison. Cause of death would be declared as “confusion.”&lt;/del&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
2. I got sidetracked and did something else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regardless, now that I’m free to say and do what I want, I can happily say that I am moving to Madison and I couldn’t be happier. Paige got a job at Epic Systems. I’m following her there. I’ll admit I was hesitant about the move at first. After talking about it, I realized that the main reason I didn’t want to go was because I was afraid. It’s usually best to ignore fear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been throwing around the phrase ‘Lifestyle Engineering’ a fair amount when talking about moving to Madison. With two years of city living under my belt, I feel that I’ve got a better understanding of what I want my day to day to look like. For instance, assuming I get the apartment I want, my commute will do down from an hour-and-a-half to fifteen minutes. It’s also fourty-five minutes by bike, which has been my dream commute since I learned what a commute really is. With this dream apartment I’ll also be just a two blocks from Paige (the best!), a block from the lake (great!), living with Mr. Tony Susan Darling (groovy!), and I’ll be downtown (super!). Everything has been chosen carefully, so all I need to do is keep trying to be interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My new job is exciting, cool, and fast paced. It’s also terrifying because I’m incredibly under-qualified, but — again — I’m working my best on ignoring fear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you come to Madison to visit. It’s close to all of my favorite places, so both of us — me and you — don’t have an excuse to not see each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;line-height:150%;&quot;&gt;———//———&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My friend Andrew Calderon, who I’ve always called Pescado, also blogs. He’s a phenomenal writer and writes on really interesting topics. You can check out his most recent post [here].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;line-height:150%;&quot;&gt;———//———&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m hoping in the next few months to convert my website from a Wordpress website to my own website. If you have any expertise in website creation, I might be reaching out to you for some hot tips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;line-height:150%;&quot;&gt;———//———&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading. Maybe I’ll get the courage (ignore fear) to publish something a little more creative. Anyway, feel free to drop me a message at kidman007@gmail.com. Let’s catch up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p1&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.5;font-style:inherit;font-weight:inherit;&quot;&gt;Love,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p1&quot;&gt;Andrew&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Twitter in the Most Hallowed of Places</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/musings/2015/06/24/twitter-in-the-most-hallowed-of-places/"/>
   <updated>2015-06-24T18:39:28-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/musings/2015/06/24/twitter-in-the-most-hallowed-of-places</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was the middle of the day in a bathroom stall on the ninth floor of the Catamaran headquarters when I realized I needed to change my relationship with Twitter. My phone was in my hands with the iconic blue bird glowing on my screen. I blinked and wondered long I had been sitting there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t long ago I actually wanted to understand Twitter better; now I wish I understood it less. Friends and coworkers were always talking about conversations they had and the interesting articles people shared on Twitter. Apparently, comedians say funny things on there as well. I like funny. At that point, I still didn’t understand Twitter. I didn’t know who I should follow, or where to find good content. I was stranger in a party everyone else was familiar with. I wanted in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I made it my mission to get the most out of Twitter. I followed modern entrepreneur personalities I admire, such as Tim Ferriss and James Altucher. I followed podcasters I enjoyed like Alex Blumburg and John Hodgeman. I looked into the “Weird Twitter” subculture, which is — unsurprisingly — weird. The list goes on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few months of pretending to like Twitter, I finally realized that I was going to Twitter willingly — I actually liked it. I checked it often and it became a nice break in my day. I was honestly embarrassed about how happy — the word “gushed” might be the best description of how I felt — I was when my favorite economist, Russ Roberts (@EconTalker), &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/EconTalker/status/609355119306665984&quot;&gt;responded to my Tweet&lt;/a&gt;. I was glowing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I checked Twitter at my desk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I checked Twitter while driving my car. (danger!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I checked Twitter at the gym.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was sitting in the most hallowed and private places for a cube warrior: the bathroom stall, when I realized that I was checking Twitter too much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(It’s gross, I get it, but bear with me.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The stall is the perfect place to check your phone — so I shouldn’t have felt self conscious about checking Tweets in there. It’s one of the few private places in an office where you can’t be seen — image is important (or so they say). Though I was seeing a lot of cool things in the &quot;Twitterverse,&quot; I realized that I was trying to escape my day — my reality — by filling any momentary void in my day with a massive mental download of media while in the bathroom. I had become the Scarface of Twitter (deluded — not murderous or coked out or the king).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I came to this realization, I made a swift decision — a instant promise to myself. Before I check Twitter while in the most hallowed of places, I must journal. I must write one-hundred words before I read dozen of one-hundred-and-forty word snippets. I must create something before I blindly consume.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far it’s worked, and It’s made me feel a lot better. Maybe tomorrow I’ll find another way to create more. Maybe not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;line-height:150%;&quot;&gt;———//———&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s summer time now, so I’ve been trying lots of new things and doing new things too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just had my first improv show with my class. I like to over-analyze how I did, but I know in my heart of hearts we did great for our first time. My whole family watched me, which was great. Two of my good friends, Matt and T. Susan Darling, came down to see me from Wisconsin, which was also great. Paige was there — great greatness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to build my own website. I have a website now — you’re looking at it — but I want to actually build a website. In order to achieve this goal, I’ve started using &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.freecodecamp.com/&quot;&gt;FreeCodeCamp.com&lt;/a&gt;, which has been a good learning experience. I’m still a long way off before I can do anything on my own, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paige is in Prague. Jared is in Ireland. I miss them a lot. On the other hand, I’ve now got more time to write my blog. It’s better when they’re here, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m reading a few books right now. “Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance” and “Cosmos.” Both are great. I'll probably need to read something simple and light to ground me after I'm done with these books, like Kafka.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;line-height:150%;&quot;&gt;———//———&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for taking the time to read this! I really appreciate you! If you’d like to be added to the mailing list, send me an email at kidman007@gmail.com or Tweet at me @kidman007 (fuel my habit).&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Chaos (lite)</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/musings/2015/05/18/chaos-lite/"/>
   <updated>2015-05-18T04:00:28-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/musings/2015/05/18/chaos-lite</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;“And then the roof fell in.” I’ve been waiting for a sentence like this to happen for a while. I’ve been looking for a focal point — a conversation starter. Other things have happened — curious things, but I have been having trouble with finding the magical sentence that has you, my faithful reader, drawn in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was happy. I had gotten Paige interested in my book, “How Not to be Wrong.” It’s a fun book — like Freakanomics with a focus on math instead of Econ. Paige — being a math major — became interested. We were reading on my Kindle together. It was cute. I was happy. We looked over at the ceiling — it was making a cracking noise. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then the roof fell in. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paige had pointed out the cracks in the ceiling of her apartment previously. “The cracks are getting bigger,” she would say. “I wouldn’t worry about it,” I would say. I was wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s times like these I realize that I prefer it when things are slightly wrong. In music, I like it when the singer can’t quite sing well, or the guitar is a little too noisy. Sure, in life I appreciate it when things are going well. Paige and I went to yoga, we ate schwarma, we enjoyed the good weather. We even watched three episodes of House of Cards. All of these things, though fun, are not the things I remember. I remember shouting as the plaster fell from ceiling next to my face. I remember the silence as we processed the what happened. Was there really a hole in her ceiling? Is that something that happens?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are often told if we *succeed* at different things we will be happy. Do a good job at work. Exercise. Get brunch. Sometimes though it’s better to be scared; it’s good to be surprised. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;————//————&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve had more energy lately, so I’ve been able to do some “Andrew things.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been reading a lot of books, which is good, because books make your brain larger. Like I mentioned before, I’m going through “How Not to be Wrong.” It’s been a great way to connect with math again without opening a difficult text book. I finished Dave Egger’s book, “A Heartbreaking Work of Staggering Genius,” last week. It was a great read. I found, however, that it was messing with how I write. It made my — already sporadic — way of writing even more all over the place. I’m reading a book on yoga called “Light on Yoga,” because I know that even though I’ll never be able to bench 200 lbs, I might be able to touch my toes. Unfortunately, I’ve found reading doesn’t make you more flexible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started a sci-fi book called 2313. I’m not sure if I’ll stick with it, because it’s massive, but we’ll see. I’m flying through this book by improvisors Tj and Dave. The writing and the organization of the book is bad, but the concepts are great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m working on learning how to write JavaScript. Codeacademy.com has been a really good resource. The class is engaging enough for me to keep on it — even after it gets more difficult after the basics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Improv is going well as well. My class is great. We have started to meet outside of class to practice, which, so far, has been very successful. In June, we’ll have our first performance. I really can’t wait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve started listening to rap. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;———//———&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading. I hope you have a killer day. I hope tomorrow is better. I hope the day after that is even better.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Faking Real Life Convincingly</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2015/03/04/faking-real-life-convincingly/"/>
   <updated>2015-03-04T16:00:14-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2015/03/04/faking-real-life-convincingly</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been trying to write this post for a while now. It’s about something that makes me very happy — in addition to my wonderful girlfriend, Paige. It’s about improv.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The interesting thing about struggling writing about improv is that it goes against the ideas of improv. For instance, there are no mistakes in improv — only happy accidents and opportunities. There isn’t any fear in improv — only showing off your best weird self.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I write about improv, this new passion of mine, I worry about mistakes. I am afraid that I won’t articulate the feelings accurately. If I can’t do that, why bother write about the feelings at all? This has resulted in me rewriting this post several times. This is the last time I’ll write this post. I promise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;——//——&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Improv is all about relationships,” Kimmie told us as she walked back and forth in front of the class. “It’s not about being funny; being funny will come. Trust me. Give the audience a reason to care about the scene.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kimmie is my improv teacher at The Second City. She is also a badass — a hilarious, outrageous, enthusiastic, and weird badass. Working with her and my classmates over the last two months has — quite simply — made my life better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I first signed up for improv classes, I thought that I would learn how to be funny. My internal monologue told me that that I’m already hilarious and fearless. I thought that’s all it took to be a great improviser. Improv classes, I assumed, would be a cake walk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After every exercise, which is usually filled with false starts and stumbles, Kimmie asks us, “Well, what did we learn?” I always want to respond with “a lot.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It turns out improv is really hard. To be successful at it, you have to behave like a good friend to your partner:&lt;br /&gt;
You have to listen.&lt;br /&gt;
You have to react.&lt;br /&gt;
You have to add something to the conversation.&lt;br /&gt;
You need to be open.&lt;br /&gt;
And you can’t be afraid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Improv puts a magnifying glass on the way we behave. Of course the scene is better when you listen to your partner, listening is the key to other interactions, why not improv scenes? Of course a scene is going to be better when you have a relationship at the center of everything, conversations in general are better when there is a relationship. The more realism and attention you bring to the table, the better you do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This applies to both life and improv.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The class is full of these revelations. It’s doing all of these things that we should be doing anyway. It’s not about fabricating reality. It’s about creating an alternate reality (the difference is subtle but significant). This challenge makes it fun and keeps me coming back for more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My new improv friends are great. All of the people are young, enthusiastic about the art form,  about hanging out, and watching improv shows. It’s like I found a secret group of goofy people that were hiding until now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The group is interesting because everyone is very different. We all have different interests and careers, but everyone in the class is the sort of person who would sign up for an introductory improv class. In other words, everyone is a little weird, inexperienced, and willing to pay money to make a fool of themselves. We are getting drinks after class tonight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s exciting to be with these people because we are excited to be together. Some of us are already talking about performing. On a stage. With an audience. I expect you to be there, reader.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Improv is good for Paige and I as well. It an outlet for us to explore the city. It’s an outlet for us to see new people. While I haven’t persuaded her to sign up for a class yet, I’m really happy we’ve found something new we can enjoy together. It means we we’ll watch less Netflix, but I’m okay with that. The more things we do together the better! Paige + improv = Pimprov, which is Russian for love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonight I start the second level of improv classes. Though I won't have Kimmie teaching me, she has promised the other teachers are quite good as well. Most of the people from my first class have joined the second class. Today I'll be better than I was yesterday. Maybe someday I'll be quite good. I'll hold my breath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;——//——&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading! I like improv. I wish I could do a better job explaining my feelings about it. Let me know if you want to catch up! Let me know if you want to be on the email list! Shoot me a message at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:andrew.h.kraemer@gmail.com&quot;&gt;andrew.h.kraemer@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll probably write a more comprehensive post about improv after I get a bit more experience.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Five Minute Blog Post</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2015/02/20/five-minute-blog-post/"/>
   <updated>2015-02-20T15:08:03-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2015/02/20/five-minute-blog-post</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My computer at work is taking an especially long time to start up this morning, so I figured I should take a few minutes and write a blog post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First off, &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/3ZYis9zlG1tR1tQ6zDCTfO&quot;&gt;here &lt;/a&gt;is a really good playlist I made. I called &quot;The Greatest Thirty Seconds.&quot; Unintentionally -- and ironically -- this is the longest playlist I've made.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I haven't written in a while for a few reasons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First off, I'm lazy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second, my last post -- the post about fainting on an airplane -- was far and away the most successful post I've done. The pressure is on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Third, I've been filling a lot of my time with my new improv class. I'll talk a lot about improv in the next post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fourth, I'm trying my best to finish Sho Gun. It's an awesome book, and I've learned a lot from it. I wish I could better articulate why the book is interesting. Usually I tell people, &quot;ShoGun is great. The Japanese thought about everything in a completely different way than the westerners did. They killed themselves a lot.&quot; While all of this is true, it's not very insightful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fifth, I've been taking myself too seriously. I don't write serious very well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sixth, I recently learned that you should still try to do Yoga even if you have a metal rod fuzed to your spine. Even though you can't do any of the poses, you can still say you tried.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've been working on meditating again. I meditate in my car before I walk into work. Sometimes I open my eyes and I see people who park next to me staring at me through my window.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wave at them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, it seems my computer is working again. I plan on having another, complete, post this weekend. I just felt I had to share something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andrew&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Unfasten Your Seatbelt</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/12/16/unfasten-your-seatbelt/"/>
   <updated>2014-12-16T22:11:20-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/12/16/unfasten-your-seatbelt</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This post is a little different from other things I've done. I wanted to share a story with you today:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was on a flight headed home after five days with my family. I was in my seat reading Hamlet because I like to pretend I'm sophisticated. I had just finished the scene where the ghost of Hamlet's father commands Hamlet to take revenge on his murderer and put my book down. I'm mentioning this now because later I'll say &quot;I looked like a ghost.&quot; This is foreshadowing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I put the book down for two reasons. (1) My Shakespeare tolerance is low, and (2) I was dangerously close to vomiting in my seat (unrelated to Shakespeare). Not wanting to disturb the man with the glasses next to me, I grabbed the &quot;sick bag&quot; from the front seat pocket and stood to go to the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As soon as I got out of my seat, I broke into a cold sweat and started to get tunnel vision. I tried my best to keep it cool while I walked to the lavatory. &quot;I think I'm fainting,&quot; I thought to myself. &quot;I'd rather not faint in the aisle.&quot; I felt my legs slowly giving out, and I grabbed the seats for support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My vision went completely black. I heard people asking if I was okay. I must have been guided to a seat, but I don't remember exactly what happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I vomited in my bag without being able to see. People were trying to be helpful, but they didn't know how to help. I felt people giving me napkins. I had so many napkins, no vision, and very little hand eye coordination. My brain was very hazy. I didn't really have a good sense of what was going around me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;Are you okay?&quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&quot;I'm okay&quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&quot;Are you okay?&quot;&lt;br /&gt;
I'm fine, seriously. I'm just fainting. People faint. I wish I wasn't making people so nervous.&lt;br /&gt;
Beep. &quot;Any medical professionals please come to the cabin.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;
Medical professionals? They have the wrong idea.&lt;br /&gt;
&quot;Are you okay?&quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&quot;I'm okay&quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&quot;You are not okay.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;
What does that mean? I'm not okay? I'm nervous. I'm very sleepy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was laid down across a row of seats. Phrases such as, &quot;He's in shock.&quot; &quot;Raise his legs.&quot; and &quot;Unbutton his shirt, I can't find his pulse,&quot; slowly registered in my head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a result of my legs being raised, my vision came back slowly, and I saw the black and white image of a woman's face above me. She looked like a Japanese ink painting. She asked me questions, and I was able to give answers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I looked down as another woman was applying a defibrillator to my chest. I looked around and saw fifteen people leaning over their seats looking at me. This made me very uncomfortable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Within a few minutes, I was talking and I could see. I answered a lot of questions to the two nurses who helped me -- both named Anne (thank you Annes) -- and the doctor with the gold chain around his neck (thank you doctor with the gold chain around your neck). After that, they filled me in on what happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had a vasovagal episode, which is an incorrect response to a change in blood pressure. All of the blood in my body went to my core, like it does with hypothermia, which caused me to lose consciousness. This response was do to a lack of eating, dehydration, prolonged sitting, and the change in air pressure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My face had been entirely blue for a few minutes. &quot;You looked like a ghost,&quot; Ann, the OBGYN nurse, said. &quot;So I slapped you repeatedly in the face.&quot; I had no idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The surrounding passengers were wide-eyed as I sat up. They were concerned and I tried my best to look unconcerned. I was concerned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn't have a pulse. It's hard to not become overly philosophical about this sort of thing, but I'm okay with that because it's how I feel. I thought I would be more scared than I was. I think I actually took it quite well. I realized that death is something that happens. We don't need to be afraid of it -- we shouldn't -- but it is important to be aware of it. It makes me excited to do things and invest in the people who I love. I know it's sappy, but it's the way I feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We landed safely. I cracked a few jokes and walked off the plane. I drank five cans of orange juice, and ate Popeyes before going to my connecting flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I left Hamlet in the terminal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading! If you would like to be added to the email list, please shoot me a message at andrew.h.kraemer@gmail.com. Send me a message even if you are on the email list -- Dan Thoresen does. We have great chats.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Tom Cruise Is Mentioned Twice in This Blog Post</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/11/21/tom-cruise-is-mentioned-twice-in-this-blog-post/"/>
   <updated>2014-11-21T15:23:27-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/11/21/tom-cruise-is-mentioned-twice-in-this-blog-post</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes I wish I wasn't so impressionable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other week I watched Jerry McGuire with Paige. There is one scene where Tom Cruise casually does handstand pushups against a wall. I thought to myself, &quot;If Tom Cruise can do it, I can do it.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is only one place in my apartment where I can do handstand pushups. The handstand location is a confined space between my refrigerator and my backdoor. Everywhere else I run the risk of either knocking Jared's art off the wall or creating foot prints in our living room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I learned two things from doing handstand push-ups:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can do a few pushups before my arms give out. It's a good feeling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The realization that my arms are about to give out while upside-down in a confined space is a bad feeling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Falling in a confined space while upside-down is a worse feeling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My point is, just because Tom Cruise can do something, doesn't mean you should.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It also doesn’t mean you shouldn’t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had been struggling all day to write how interesting it is that some systems are more durable than others. I stole this concept from Nassim Taleb’s book “Anti-Fragile.” Some organizations and social constructs seem to go on forever; they are solid. Other systems fall by the wayside – quickly forgotten. I wanted to explore this concept of long lasting systems within the framework of my visit to my fraternity this weekend. I wanted this to be a persuasive essay, and I wanted it to be &lt;em&gt;good.&lt;/em&gt; There was potential to make this a very interesting piece. I know this because Jared told me so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I couldn't do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would write a few sentences and cringe. &quot;That sounds too faux poetic,&quot; I would grumble. I followed this up with, &quot;Andrew, you are pretentious and you don't actually know what faux means.&quot; So, I did what most successful writers do: gave up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes I wish writing came as naturally to me as talking does. I &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:line-through;&quot;&gt;can&lt;/span&gt; talk endlessly about everything and anything. I used to be jealous of people in college who complained about having to edit a paper down to the page maximum. I never had that problem in my entire life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've changed my attitude. Though it’s not easy, writing makes me think. Writing makes me say what I think more carefully. People forget conversations. Ideas in conversations die with people who speak them. Ideas written down have the potential to live on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:line-through;&quot;&gt;I guess that's why some systems, such as the written word, have continued for so many thousands of years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps not being comfortable with writing how interesting long lasting systems are is an indication that it would have been a boring essay. Who knows?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my mind there are two different kinds of movies: Movies that my dad likes, movies that my Uncle Tommy likes. Anything else probably isn't worth watching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both my dad and his brother, Tommy, are big movie fans. My dad, I would say, is more of a traditionalist. His favorite movie is &lt;em&gt;Get Shorty &lt;/em&gt;starring John Travolta. Other examples of &quot;Dad movies&quot; include:  anything that stars Tom Cruise, Classic Musicals, the Die Hard series, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Uncle Tommy is a bit more artsy. Though he also likes the classics, he leans towards less traditional movies. They include: Wes Anderson films, and that one Australian indie film that I couldn't understand a word of where everybody died.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should see the movie “Birdman” as soon as possible. I wasn’t planning on seeing it, but Paige said we should go see it. It's an Uncle Tommy film starring Michael Keaton. It's about a washed up actor who is trying to revitalize his career by doing theater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie is incredibly well done. The acting is killer -- it is a movie about acting after all. The filmography has a very stream of conscious feel to it by the way the camera bounces from character.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's weird and smart and fun, which happen to be three of my favorite things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you enjoyed this blog! If you want to talk, reach out to me at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Kidman007@gmail.com&quot;&gt;Kidman007@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;. I like you. Life is short (&lt;a href=&quot;http://fourhourworkweek.com/2009/04/24/on-the-shortness-of-life-an-introduction-to-seneca/&quot;&gt;but actually not that short&lt;/a&gt;). So let's catch up. We could talk about music or ideas or ideas in music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any constructive criticism, such as &quot;why don't you ever have a point in the things you write&quot; or “this post was too long and boring”, please let me know. I -- like you -- am working on getting better every day.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Introspection is So Post-Post-Post Modern</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/10/27/introspection-is-so-post-post-post-modern/"/>
   <updated>2014-10-27T12:03:42-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/10/27/introspection-is-so-post-post-post-modern</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some general updates:&lt;br /&gt;
-I saw Foxygen live. It was amazing. I saw the show with my cousin, Shawn. We had an awesome time. It was like choosing to walk into a burning building.&lt;br /&gt;
-I saw The Rural Alberta Advantage live. I saw it with some work friends and Paige. It was an awesome time, though the opening band made me feel uncomforable.&lt;br /&gt;
-Here is this week's playlist. I called it &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/1le3FTeKwLBRCeucJD0mtQ&quot;&gt;Don't Spoil The End&lt;/a&gt;,&quot; which is incredibly cheesy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And now for some babble: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'd like to remove the word &quot;I&quot; from my speech. I find that I am always talking about myself. I'm talking about myself right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I understand that my experience is really the only one I can truly relate to, but I still wish I didn't think and talk as if everything was about me. I often find myself interrupting other people's stories just to point out how I have a similar story and can relate to them. Even if I tried, it would be tough for me, however, to communicate if my vernacular did not include the word &quot;I&quot;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The gangly redheaded person who is writing this blog post would certainly struggle with communicating without a common one letter pronoun that rhymes with eye, aye, and goodbye. For one, telling personal stories would be completely out of the question. The redheaded person would either need to tell stories that happened to other people -- which wouldn't always make sense -- or, more likely, he would need to tell stories in the third person. His audience would hate this. Alternatively, the redhead could constantly need to speak as if he was giving a lecture, which would wrongly imply that the redhead has any legitimacy outside of his own experience:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is always important to avoid speaking of oneself. Removing &quot;I&quot; from your language opens up the opportunity to truly listen and engauge. People constantly busy themselves with their inner monologue -- their inner worries. Thinking in this way closes off the beauty of wider world. Putting others in the spotlight is the best way to bring internal happiness. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess what I'm trying to say is that I'm working on my voice. It seems that every sentence's subject is the word &quot;I&quot; and it's been tough to try to work around that.  I don't want everything to be about me, but what else would I talk about on a blog entitled: &quot;Andrew Kraemer, Now in Technicolor&quot;? I guess I like using &quot;I&quot; because it makes saying &quot;I don't know&quot; easier. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don't know. I don't know.   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently got a year of my life back. It was very refreshing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stupid thoughts constantly fly through my head, and I question if  I am doing the right thing in my career. I am doing enough work? Am I doing enough side projects outside of my job description. Do I like my work? Am I leaving enough time for myself? How much do I hate my commute? Am I keeping up with my hobbies? Am I writing my silly blog enough? Am I asking silly questions too much?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With these thoughts I often, and unnecessarily, feel that I am behind. I had a vision that I will be doing something incredible by the time I am twenty-five. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, while foolishly asking foolish questions, I felt a particularly nagging feeling that I was behind on my timeline. &quot;I'm twenty-four and I haven't even discovered what my incredible thing is,&quot; I thought to myself. I mentioned this  feeling to my friend, Micah. Micah is the same age as I am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It turns out that I am actually twenty-three. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a relief. I have another year! Success doesn't have a timeline, and -- more importantly -- success is what you make of it. I've decided to stop worrying about inconsequential timelines. Instead, I'll focus on real problems, such as knowing my age and not leaving my lunch on the kitchen counter. If I have time, I'll worry about the word &quot;I&quot; too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading. I realize this post had a bit more &quot;mental wrestling&quot; instead of whimsy, but sometimes you have to write what's on your mind. I miss you. Shoot me a message at kidman007@gmail.com and let's catch up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andrew&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>And Now a Word from Our Sponsors</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/10/02/and-now-a-word-from-our-sponsors/"/>
   <updated>2014-10-02T16:32:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/10/02/and-now-a-word-from-our-sponsors</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Recently I've been putting a lot of pressure on myself to write a really clever blog post. I'd like the post to be funny, interesting, and insightful. I would like that post to be about five-hundred words. I would like that post to be amazing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you just need to forget about your anxieties and hope for the best. Here's to hoping for the best.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have been really enjoying the band Foxygen. Normally, when I find new music, I will listen to a band only a handful of times before moving on to something else. Foxygen is the exception to this rule. For the past two months I've been listening to Foxygen, specifically the album &quot;21st Century Ambassadors of Peace and Love, seemingly nonstop. I like the band because they are not the best at anything. They are not the most technical band, nor are they the edgiest band. All of their music always sounds a little off for one reason or another. They do, however, have an incredible amount of charm and heart. I like charm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of their songs is on &lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/0aPLNzwUZ731Ip8LjVigLu&quot;&gt;this great playlist I made&lt;/a&gt; (I think this is one of my best).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I played this album in the car one day when I was with Paige. We were driving with the windows down and were bobbing our heads. She smiled, looked at me and said, &quot;Andrew, I really don't like this music.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe I'm just crazy. I'll let you make your own opinion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My ego has been getting bigger recently. I've noticed this because people have told me. Hearing this hurts my ego, because I've always thought of myself as a humble person, which -- I've realized -- is probably an egocentric comment in itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm also working on being more thoughtful. Sometimes I get a bit too focused on what is directly in front of me, rather than what is important to me. I'm working on changing my focus back to you, my friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm my own work in progress, I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wonder if cavemen were dyslexic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was lying awake wondering this last night -- as one does.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If they were, I wonder how they identified it. I'm guessing that the caveman-children were not at caveman school where they would write in their caveman spelling notebooks. I'm also guessing that the caveman kindergartener who had a more difficult time writing words like &quot;moose&quot; and &quot;hunt&quot; and &quot;pizza&quot; would not of had a teacher who identified a problem. It's also likely that the inability to spell correctly would not of resulted in a caveman-parent-teacher conference that would have caused the caveman-parents to be concerned, which would result in the eventual diagnosis of dyslexia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My guess is that dyslexic cavemen were just cavemen. Situations highlight strengths and weaknesses; strengths and weakness are not absolute or universally applicable, even though it may feel like that sometimes. A caveman doesn't need to be able to read Shakespeare or tell which way left is. He only needs to kill the moose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you liked this post. I feel like it was a bit all over the place, but that's ok. If you want to catch up or have any feedback, please don't hesitate to email me at kidman007@gmail.com Thanks for reading, and I hope you have a great day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll end this post with a quote by Abraham Lincoln, &lt;i&gt;&quot;Sometimes you need to talk about your weaknesses and then talk about cavemen in order to unite your thoughts.&quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How I Had My First Mexican Car-Crash and Other Stories of NYC</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/08/27/how-i-had-my-first-mexican-car-crash-and-other-stories-of-nyc/"/>
   <updated>2014-08-27T01:51:22-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/08/27/how-i-had-my-first-mexican-car-crash-and-other-stories-of-nyc</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends, &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had a great time in New York this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The journey had a few bumps along the way, but, after landing in Newark at one-in-the-morning -- rather than the intended airport, Laguardia, at eleven-thirty, I knew the trip was going to be memorable. I stayed at my Aunt's apartment on the lower west side of Manhattan. In the morning, I had four cups of coffee, ate delicious Chinese food, and talked about life with my aunt. Life's a good conversation topic; it beats the news. My aunt has a very interesting life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I left my aunt and met up with my friend, Andrew, in one of the oldest coffee shops in New York. We planned our day. And then we walked. We walked all over the place. Sometimes we walked into parks that were on train tracks. I don't know what they are called, but they were beautiful. Sometimes we walked into bars. While we walked we talked. We talked a lot about ideas. We often disagreed with each others ideas, but we always listened to each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, we sat on the roof of Andrew's apartment in Astoria. He has a great view of the Manhattan skyline which we enjoyed over a few beers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was right around this time when I realized that I was allergic to cats. My allergic reaction resulted me sneezing an &lt;i&gt;incredible&lt;/i&gt; amount, and my entire face -- especially my eyes -- swelled to the point in which &lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ADdOviil.jpg&quot;&gt;I was not recognizable&lt;/a&gt;. I also had a general feeling of foreboding. It's interesting having your body react violently to something as harmless as a kitten -- especially such a nice kitten. It's almost sad that cats, though very cute, are now no more to me than poison. That's ok, though. There are always dogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was planning on going to the MoMA on my final day before catching my flight. This didn't happen. Instead, I sat in a nice coffee shop chugging coffee to counteract the effect of the Benedryl so I wouldn't fall asleep and miss my flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had a great time in New York this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading! If you have any suggestions about what I should write about or want to check in, please reach out to me at kidman007@gmail.com or in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Slight Change</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/08/21/slight-change/"/>
   <updated>2014-08-21T01:24:44-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/08/21/slight-change</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In an effort to come out with more regular posts, I've decided to make some of the posts shorter. This is one of the short posts. Over the last year-or-so of writing the blog, I've developed a bit of a standard format to the blog. It often looks something like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A brief, often humorous, and occasionally odd introduction. This is usually an observation that doesn't warrant further investigation. It's usually just something I noticed. For example, I could write about &lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Pey8ijf.png&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; Excel art I made while I was on a phone call.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A link to my playlist of the post that almost no one will listen to. I listen to it, which is why I say 'almost'. I'll mention a few tracks I really like and why I really like them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A slightly longer &quot;essay.&quot; Normally when I write these I just write about something I've been thinking about a lot recently and distill it into around three-hundred to five-hundred words.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another brief and humorous -- often self-deprecating -- observation. Perhaps it's an awkward moment. Perhaps it's an admission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another &quot;essay&quot; of sorts. Usually, if I've gotten people to read this far, I'll write about something that I think is a bit more serious. Usually it still ends up being a little silly -- which I can't always help. I like to think of this part as a &quot;writing in a journal&quot; section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A thank you to the readers and a comment -- without fail -- that states my frustration at the infrequency of my posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that's it. That's what I do. I like the format. I think it allows me to hit a bunch of different topics without needing to dive too deep into anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think like writing this way because I don't like writing in detail. I assume that the reader understands all of the thinking that goes into each post. Paige and Jared hear each &quot;essay&quot; eight or nine times before I actually write anything. I assume you can fill in the cracks like they can, which is silly. How could you know everything that goes on in my brain?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an attempt to make myself uncomfortable, I plan on having a few posts that are longer and more focused in addition to the more frequent short posts. I don't expect them to be as fun or as easy as the standard format but that's ok with me. You might learn something. I'll definitely learn something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading. You are great. I am great. We are all great. If you want to talk about greatness, email me at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:kidman007@gmail.com&quot;&gt;kidman007@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;. Thank you for taking the time.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>A Plethora of Brows</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/08/13/a-plethora-of-brows/"/>
   <updated>2014-08-13T03:01:31-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/08/13/a-plethora-of-brows</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I received some constructive criticism from a few friends recently about the blog. Though It was not the criticism I expected, I welcomed it nonetheless. I was told that my blog can be too high brow because of some obscure references I make. I was surprised because I didn't think my blog had any brow at all. At the most, I assumed that my blog was primarily very low or lo- to-middle-brow -- also known as mustache. I appreciate the feedback, but I don't really know how to address this except for saying, &quot;ok,&quot; and moving on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, let's move on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've made a playlist for this week. I decided to name it &lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/4WAL87PUiBvinZ6npI3jgB&quot;&gt;&quot;Shirt Starched and Ready for Battle.&quot;&lt;/a&gt; It has some music that I like on it. I've been doing a bit less music exploration recently. I became a bit supersaturated with music from Pitchfork Music Festival and have not quite gotten back into my next music discovery phase yet. I hope you like it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've decided to start a business. I'm optimistic, and I have the upmost confidence that I will fail. It's not that I don't think I can make something happen; I just know that there are a few things that are going to make starting a business difficult. As I see it, there are three major impediments to my startup. All of which are terrible, typical excuses that all aspiring entrepreneurs run into.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first main problem is that I don't have a lot of time. I realize that saying I don't have a lot of time is a classic excuse but that's how I feel. It's tough to do a full work day, have a one-and-a-half hour commute, work out, write a blog -- however infrequently it actually gets published, talk to my roommate, feed myself, see my girlfriend, get the seven hours of sleep I never seem to get, and enjoy my many time consuming hobbies. Despite all of that, I'm ready -- today at least to make something that is mine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second roadblock to my startup success is the fact that I don't have a great idea; in fact, I don't have any ideas whatsoever. Whenever I ask people for &quot;easy&quot; company ideas, I always get the same answer: sell drugs. While I appreciate the input, I already work for a drug company. I don't think not being inspired will cause my business' failure. I know that if I think hard enough and often enough something -- no matter how mundane -- will come to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The final thing that is preventing me from starting is that I have no idea of how to start a business at all. I have all sorts of questions such as, do I pay taxes? When does it become an actual business? And so on. However, the reason I am starting a company that I know will fail is that I really want to &lt;del&gt;experience the embarrassing and debilitating pain of failure&lt;/del&gt; learn what it is like to take ownership of an idea (and get paid for it too).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, all of that being said, I'm excited and ready to do &lt;em&gt;something&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a lot of opportunity out there. Technology lowers transaction costs while also making communication and automation easy. There are plenty of bad business ideas that succeed and plenty of good business ideas that don't. I want to start a business now because I want to. I don't need permission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've come to realize that I'm a victim of marketing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I realized this after I got my cool travel coffee mug in the mail. I'm happy to have the mug. It has a cool, hip color scheme. It has the words &quot;barista standard 12 oz cup&quot; on the side; I don't know what this means, but it sounds cool. It's also made of post consumer plastic, which means -- and don't quote me on this -- it has something to do with the environment, and it's very 'in' right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While it may be 'hip', 'cool', and 'in', I spent $20 on a plastic coffee cup that doesn't keep my coffee warm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My roommate also just told me that I can borrow his thermos. He has two he's never used before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my strengths is my enthusiasm for saying yes. I've found that people respond to this with enthusiasm. It makes them smile, and it makes people like me. I'm vain; I like the feeling of being liked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, I've come to realize, however, that this enthusiasm for saying yes to everything can also be a weakness. Because people like to hear yes, they will come back and ask for something else, knowing that I will likely be agreeable and interested in participating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm very blessed with all of the opportunities I have and the people I have connections with. But I've found in &quot;the post college world&quot; -- where one has less time for everything and an ever-increasing amount of responsibilities -- that I need to learn how to become comfortable with saying &quot;no.&quot; I also get quite tired. I run myself to the bone. As a result, I'm working on being more thoughtful with my time. So, if you find that I decline one of your offers, I hope you understand where I'm coming from.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made an impulse Craig's List purchase. For $100, I am now the proud owner of: a five person tent, a Coleman gas grill, two camping chairs, a cooking kit, a mess kit, and camping cooking tools. I picked everything up from Ron.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I drove up to Ron's mobile home, I saw him standing next to his car with a big closed lipped grin that hid his missing teeth. Ron is sixty-seven years old. He was incredibly nice and very excited to sell me his gear. Ron pulled out one piece of equipment after another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;This is the tent,&quot; he told me. &quot;It's big. It's not tall enough for you, but it's big.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the display, we talked a bit. He promised that though the gear was good even though it was old. He told me about how he driven his motorcycle across the United States with all of this gear with his honey. He's seen a lot of beautiful things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was sad driving away with Ron's things, but I'm very excited to make sure the camping continues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, as always, for taking some time to read the blog. It really does mean a lot. If you have any questions, any business ideas, or just want to say &quot;hey, what's up?&quot;, please send me an email at kidman007@gmail.com. I look forward to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Best Bad Idea I've Had in Years</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/06/27/the-best-bad-idea-ive-had-in-years/"/>
   <updated>2014-06-27T02:32:48-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/06/27/the-best-bad-idea-ive-had-in-years</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello my friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before we do anything, you should check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/56nGcKM7jhj0NwpVzp38Qt&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; playlist. I think there are a bunch of sweet tunes on it that you should check out (especially the last track).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm a very impressionable person. This quirk manifested itself when I was listening to the &quot;Tim Ferriss Show,&quot; hosted by Tim Ferriss, writer of &quot;The Four Hour Work Week.&quot; Each episode he interviews some interesting, creative, high-performing individual and has a great conversation. In the last episode, I listened to him talk to a biochemist who focuses on nutrition and healthy living. Very casually, the biochemist mentioned that her breakfast every morning is a smoothie that contains the following: lots of kale, a handful of spinach, two carrots, a handful of frozen berries, an apple (optional), a banana (optional), an avocado, protein powder, and almond milk. The story intrigued me, as well as the smoothie, but I forgot about the whole thing immediately afterwords.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To my surprise, when I woke up the next morning, I found a huge bag of kale -- a pound and a half to be precise -- in my refrigerator. In addition, I found a boatload of fresh produce and more than enough protein powder to kill a horse. I'm glad to report that the smoothie was delicious and made me feel good all day. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I'm glad I actually went out and bought the materials for the smoothie, I've got no idea what to do with the remaining 1.4 pounds of kale in my fridge. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paige just graduated from Lawrence and moved to Evanston. While this may be a run-of-the-mill idea for you -- or perhaps it's simply an unsurprising statement, it's a pretty big deal for me. After going through a year of a distance relationship, it's difficult to articulate how nice it is to be in the same place as Paige, so I won't try. I will say, however, that I'm very happy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though I've made some attempts to stop thinking about the immediate future -- over thinking my career path was causing me a bit of anxiety, I have been doing a bit of day dreaming of what my midlife crisis is going to be. I've though about it a lot the last few weeks and I came up with this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1) Pack up all of my bags and move to California.&lt;br /&gt;
2) Live on the outskirts of town.&lt;br /&gt;
3) Invest all of my money into a start-up.&lt;br /&gt;
4) Ride a wave of undeserved success.&lt;br /&gt;
5) Watch both my company and relationships fall apart.&lt;br /&gt;
6) Get evicted from my house.&lt;br /&gt;
7) Have the dog walk out on me.&lt;br /&gt;
8) Starvation.&lt;br /&gt;
9) Alcoholism.&lt;br /&gt;
10) Disease.&lt;br /&gt;
11) Eventual -- and inevitable -- death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like this plan because -- unlike most dreams -- it is actually possible to achieve. Sure, hunger, disease, and abandonment -- not to mention death -- all seem a bit unsavory; I'll admit that upfront. On the other hand. however, I hear that weather in California is nice year-round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm trying to incorporate more writing into my life. I think of myself as a person who thinks. I think of myself as a person who has a good sense of humor. I really like the idea of writing my experiences and sharing them with other people via this blog on a regular basis. Unfortunately, this blog gets updated very infrequently. As I see it, I have two major roadblocks that I have to overcome in order to make this blog what I want it to be. First, is that I am lazy. I'm not too busy to write; blaming business is a form of laziness. In response to this, I've been coming up with plans and routines to enable myself to write every day. Sitting down and writing is not the only area where my laziness gets in the way; I also stall on aggregating the bits of what I write up and actually publish them.  The second roadblock is that I'm still pretty self-conscience about my writing. Unfortunately, this does not translate into me editing more, it just means I publish less. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, my friends, this is where you come in. If you have any feedback on how I write, what I write about, what you think is interesting, what you think is boring, what literary devices I use too much, what grammatical errors I make, I'd love to hear your feedback because I really am trying to learn. I'm trying to get better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I hope all is as good with you as it is with me. Send me a message at Kidman007@gmail.com. I'd love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>I Saved Latin</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/05/21/i-saved-latin/"/>
   <updated>2014-05-21T01:48:56-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/05/21/i-saved-latin</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I came up with a great idea the other day. I'm happy about the idea because I've acutally talked a few of my co-workers into doing it. Here's the idea: I'm going to bike to work. At first glance, this doesnt sound too impressive, as it is fairly common for people to ride their bike to work. And even when I explain the caveats some of you will still be wondering why this is interesting. But wait! Work for me is twenty-six miles away, and, in order to get there, I'm going to have to navigate the wild streets of Chicago before arriving at the mighty Catamaran Tower. I'm pretty excited. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently got a new bike (well, actually it's quite used). When I first saw the bike in the used bike store, it didn't have a front wheel and the handle bars were lying next to it on the floor. When my new friend John pointed at is and said, &quot;this one will fit you,&quot; he smiled. He then said, &quot;I'm not done with this one yet, but I've been working on this bike like it was one of my own.&quot; From that point on, any logic that went into buying my bike evaporated. It's a great bike and I'm happy to have it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'd like to be in a life threatening situation sometime soon. I obviously don't want to die, and I definitely don't want to go through this experience alone. The reason I want to do this is simple; traumatic experiences bring people together in ways unlike any other. You could sit on the train with someone everyday for an entire year and I'd bet that you wouldn't feel as close to that person as you would if the train flew off the tracks and you helped each other survive the burning wreckage (especially if one - or both - of you lose a limb in the process). Another part of me wants to be able to introduce someone by saying, &quot;This is my friend Alphonso. He saved my life in 2014.&quot; After that, Alhonzo and I would give a great high five with our left hands and I would say, &quot;We both lost our right arm in a tragic incident at the zoo.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really like the idea of moving around in a company. While there is sometime to be said about to having an expertise, something that you can do better than pretty much anyone, I like the idea of having a wide breadth of skills and experiences . The way I see it, it is a lot easier to pick up the basics and be proficient at a new skill than it is to gain an equivalent amount of increased expertise on a skill you are already an expert in. Also, I like the idea of cross fertilization of ideas. It's super neat when you see someone from one discipline find a way to improve another discipline because of their different perspective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was worrying for a while about my future and what I would do. Now I think I'll have just a few personal goals and try to get as much crazy and varied experiences as possible in both work and life in general.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are two things I'm working on: taking risks and saying no. I've been inundated recently by articles about entrepreneurship, and my brain has had  an inexplicable desire to try keep on trying to achieve goals or projects with a medium to high chance of failure. That being said, I also have a desire to do good work, which requires extended focus and the ability to not bite off more than I can chew. It's weird to have both desires and only have 24 hours in a day. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recommend that you pick up the collection of stories, &quot;Letter from an Unknown Woman,&quot; by Stephan Zweig. I've only read the first story , which shares the same name as the collection, and I loved it. I jumped from confused to intrigued to sad in the span of sixty pages. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I discovered Zweig by way of Wes Andrewson.  Anderson's latest film,&quot;Grand Budapest Hotel,&quot; was inspired by the works of Zweig. The movie was great and so is Zweig.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, I'm off. I feel like this post was more for me than for youbut that's ok. If you want to be added to the mailing list or just want to say hi, drop me an email at kidman007@gmail.com. I'd love to hear from you. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Edit:&lt;br /&gt;
After getting some feedback from a few loyal readers, I realized how poorly edited this post is. Rather than getting frustrated about the poor grammar that I've tried so hard to improve on, I'm going to take this post as a polite suggestion to get some sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Reality Check</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/05/03/reality-check/"/>
   <updated>2014-05-03T01:21:16-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/05/03/reality-check</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have not written anything in a while. This lack of published material is partly due to the fact that I have been busy with my new appartment. The main reason, however, is that I have been stuggling to write things that I find honest and clever. I've written some honest things, but they were boring. I've written some clever things, but they were absurd. Both things I wrote I don't think people would like reading. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other day I was writing about the absurd eighties action movie, Running Man, starring Arnold Schwartzenegger. I was trying to explain -- in an honest and clever way -- that I admire Arnold's success. Not many people have the move from Mr. Universe to international movie star to the governor of the largest state in the most powerful country in the world. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was writing this while standing in my apartment in the dark on my makeshift podium. In addition, Miles Davis' unsettling experimental jazz album, Bitches Brew, was blaring on playing on my record player. There I was, standing in the dark alone, thinking and writing about Arnold Schwartzenegger, with really bizzare music playing in the background, when I got a text from my friend. The message was in regards to a conference call I had forgotten that I had planned to disucuss the logistics of the camping camping trip my group of friends -- also known as the President's club -- were planning this summer. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I got this text a few things happened in my mind at once. The first was complete and utter disorientation. My brain could not make the cognitive leap from Arnold Schwarzenegger and unsettling jazz music to a phone call with friends. The second thing that I thought of after the text was the absolute absurdity of the situration and what this must look like from an outside view. The final thought I had before calling my friend was, &quot;why the hell am I writing about Arnold Schwartzenegger.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no playlist this week. Go into a dark room and listen to Bitches Brew. If you really need a playlist. Go &lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/1cTGuemGHnGHT5Gb5HqGns&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. It is a weird one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paige has gotten a job offer in Chicago. I'm very proud of her. I'm looking forward to not have to drive three hours to see her -- provided that the Chicago traffic doesn't throw me a curve ball.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being sick is weird, but it's not all bad. Last week I had a bit of a cold, which turned into quite a bit of a cold. At first I was fine but I got to the point where I woke up and sounded like Tom Waits. Being the &quot;responsible&quot; &quot;adult&quot; that I am, I was intent on going to despite obvious illness. Jared easily talked me out of this. I'm glad he did because I was miserable, and it was awesome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like to think that I do a lot of things and keep myself busy, so I don't usually have the time to wallow in self pitty. It was nice to catch up on that. Even though my head hurt, my sinuses hurt, I was tired, and my nose was raw from blowing my nose so much, it was really nice to do nearly nothing all day. I only left the house once because I found out that we were out of toilet paper. I'm not going to beat around the bush here, it was a terrible realization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I complained to Paige that I was feeling a little, &quot;Tiredsaddepressed with a splash of 'you are sick and will feel better in the morning. Things are good, you goof.'&quot; Paige helped me better explain this feeling: crabby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even after I was done with my sick day, my body took the rest of the week to recover and I was very tired. I feel good now. Being sick is a nice little reminder that of my fragility. It also makes feeling good feel better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------//---------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have two new fitness goals. I'd like to be able to do handstand pushups and I would also like to be able to do pull-ups in my door frame. I tried to do both of these exercises today, both ended in injury.&lt;br /&gt;
-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading my blog. Now that I have settled down my life a little bit and found a coffee shop I like, I think it will be easier for me to write my blog more regularly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email me at Kidman007@gmail.com if you want to be added to the mailing list. Please email me, even if you don't want to be added. I miss you and I'd like to catch up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andrew&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Let's Take Risks</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/03/20/lets-take-risks/"/>
   <updated>2014-03-20T02:26:10-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/03/20/lets-take-risks</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you are doing well. I'm doing excellent. I feel electric. I feel pretty alright. I hope you are feeling good as well. Here is a &lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/6xIsLnxbAN0CCeBkHBen0Z&quot;&gt;sweet&lt;/a&gt; playlist. It's called &quot;I'm the Meat, You're the Knife.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was thinking the other day, what would a dog write a blog about in a blog post. What would be their focus? What would motivate them? I'm not a dentist, and I don't have much experience with dogs. Despite this I decided that it would be fun to write a blog post as if I was a dog, so bear with me:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;l;jasdfhjk;  ;k;jasdflbhuasdbhjbhjasbu  +56255 ;ljfsaj;hasdilhhlalksdhkjhjksfgy. Woof.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dogs don't have fingers. That was a terrible idea. I hope I don't post this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's talk about something more interesting than dogs: my mother. My mom is going to Croatia for two weeks, which is a pretty long time. I don't really remember a time that my mom has been away from the family for that long. Goodbyes with parents are really special. They are awkward and a little sad. My mom said, &quot;I'm going to miss you, honey,&quot; and we hugged. Up until this point, our goodbye was a classic family moment full of love. So, of course something would have to go wrong. After our embrace, my mom looked up at me and said, &quot;I used your car. It smells really bad. You must have smelly socks in there.&quot; After that, she left to go to Croatia for two weeks without seeing another word.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Classic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I've been thinking about optimism a lot the last few weeks. It is weird because it is a good thing and a bad thing. There is one side to the optimist debate, where I feel most people are, which focuses on problems and potential setbacks, says optimism can lead to not being prepared, not being realistic, or not realizing the gravity of the situation. Then there is the other side, which I think I'm on, that focuses on the possibilities or upside of a situation. I'll also point out that optimism leads to happiness and is healthier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Both sides have helpful perspectives and a lot of the time I wish I could trade a little bit of the surprise I get from being ill prepared for a little bit more tension overall. Perhaps I'm being overly optimistic about this, but I think that I'm being realistic in looking on the bright side. Though I have gotten burned before, I feel that my attitude usually helps me more than hurts me. I'm making strives to take more precautions to avoid guilt (I don't usually feel anxious, but I will feel guilty if something goes wrong).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Maybe I'll abandon both optimism and not-optimism, which is a more positive way of stating the alternative - more negative - view: pessimism, and go with surrealism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I think this whole conversation is a monkey. Don't you think so, Zeus?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; -------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I woke up in the middle of the night and felt the urge to write something down to put on the blog. I grabbed my notebook and jotted the thought down before i went to sleep. When I woke up I saw this written down. &quot;If you want to be a world champion belly flopper, you have to like like climbing ladders.&quot; I guess it's nice to know that my sub-conscience would be a subpar motivational speaker&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; -------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had the odd experience of drinking some scotch in someone's apartment without their permission. In fact, I was in this person's apartment without permission. It's a strange situation for sure, but as my grandpa used to say, &quot;Scotch that is stolen tastes better. This is a fact.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My grandpa said a lot of funny things. Another quote of his, which I live by, is,&quot;If you put ketchup on a hotdog or mustard on a hamburger, you are a communist.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I read &lt;a href=&quot;http://lifehacker.com/10-of-the-most-important-life-lessons-i-learned-from-my-1547298543&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; article today. It reinforced my desire to do crazy things and take risks. I want to come up with a really crazy idea and run with it. I want to be able to put myself in a position where I can just come up with crazy ideas all day and run with them. I recommend you read the article.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you liked the post. I'm feeling a bit scatterbrained right now. If you would like to be added to the mailing list, shoot me an email at Kidman007@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Case of the</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/03/11/the-case-of-the/"/>
   <updated>2014-03-11T01:29:54-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/03/11/the-case-of-the</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;People write for different reasons. Some people write in order to record their thoughts; others get paid write. I'm in a different category right now. I am writing as a literal escape. This is not teenager’s escape from reality by abusing drugs and alcohol type of escape. No, I am writing as an excuse to get out of something – probably work. I am writing in order to trick myself into thinking I am being productive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I'm ok with that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are exciting things happening right now. For instance, there is this really cool playlist I made on Spotify. It's called &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/2alCBQWgoO1Dhb9I97iuV9&quot;&gt;Missing Hat&lt;/a&gt;.&quot; I hope you enjoy it. You should really listen to the song by Sun Kil Moon because it is an emotional roller coaster. You should also listen to the Turtle Giant song. It will make you stronger and better looking. The other songs are random, but I dig them, so you should check them out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though there are many things to choose from, I would say that the most exciting thing that is happening to me right now is that my curly-haired friend, Jared, and I are getting an apartment together in Chicago. I think we will name it something awesome. I’ll nominate &quot;Dudelair.&quot; I should talk to Jared.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moving is an exciting thing. It is not every day you take all of the things you have accumulated over the years as a consumer and move it somewhere else. On top of that you also sleep in a different place, which is cool. I tried to write about the apartment once with words (prose, long form, whatever). The main problem I found with the description was that it was really boring, so I have decided to make a list of &quot;Dudelair&quot; attributes and facts. Hopefully it will satisfy your probing questions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-It is four blocks north of Wrigley Field&lt;br /&gt;
-It is a brownstone building, which means it is old and has high ceilings.&lt;br /&gt;
-It has new kitchen appliances&lt;br /&gt;
-It has granite countertops&lt;br /&gt;
-It has wood floors&lt;br /&gt;
-It has a dish washer&lt;br /&gt;
-It will have Jared and me&lt;br /&gt;
-It has a very clutch in-unit washer and dryer.&lt;br /&gt;
-It has friendship&lt;br /&gt;
-It has nicely sized bedrooms with nicely sized closets&lt;br /&gt;
-With written permission, girls will be allowed visit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Dudelair will be great. There will be the making of delicious preserves and jams, beer brewing, comradery, cribbage playing, high-fives, high-fours, adventurous cooking, and adventurous eating out (when we are too lazy to cook).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I appreciate Jared's levelheaded and organized approach to life. I hope that he will appreciate my chaotic, disjointed approach to life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regardless, fingers crossed - things will probably turn out great. You should come to our housewarming party. It will be at our home and - if everything goes well - it will be warm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm very proud of myself, though it is for a pretentious reason. I'm reading Ulysses, which is pretty pretentious in itself. Anyway, I finished what most people consider &quot;The most difficult chapter&quot; – I didn’t understand most of it – and then I finished the longest chapter, which was about one-hundred and twenty-two pages. This means I'm on the home stretch. Though I've liked reading Ulysses, I'm ready to move onto something a little easier. Perhaps I'll read Crime and Punishment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I just contradicted myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm trying to figure out my five-year plan. You know, asking myself, “What do I need to do in the near future in order to accomplish things I think I'll want to do in the far future.” It is harder than I thought. One question I needed to confront is my work life. Do I want to do hardcore finance or the operations side of the business? Do I need to do more hardcore finance in order to achieve other goals I want?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I have decided to try to prepare myself as much as possible for having a cool operations position. I'm not exactly sure why. I have only two things I know that I really want to do in my future professionally: First, I want go to school. I don't know for what or for how long, but I know I'll go back. Second, I know that I want to do a dramatic occupation change. I want to push myself. I want to make myself feel uncomfortable. We will see how that goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to read something light, I encourage you to read &quot;Stories for Nighttime and Some for the Day&quot; by Ben Loory. It is a unique collection of stories by Mr. Loory. It is interesting because it is the only book that both my brother - who is twelve - and I both really enjoy. If you go &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thisamericanlife.org/radio-archives/episode/498/transcript&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and read act three, you will find yourself enthralled by a story of a man and a moose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check it out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;br /&gt;
It looks like my time to escape is coming to an end. I’ll talk to you guys next week. If you want to be put on the mailing list, email me at kidman007@gmail.com. I'm thinking about moving my blog to ghost.org, which means my link might be different next time.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>And So On</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/02/04/and-so-on/"/>
   <updated>2014-02-04T01:50:14-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/02/04/and-so-on</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope all is well with you. I know things are quite groovy with me. (Speaking of groovy, here is a &lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/7IClzoEYckViwa8P7LIOa9&quot;&gt;groovy playlist&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You probably have not noticed that it has been a while since my last post. I have noticed. I have one-hundred-and-one excuses why I haven't written in a while. You don't care about any of them, but that's ok. I've been prioritizing other things the last few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started reading &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline;&quot;&gt;Ulysses&lt;/span&gt;. It is cool. It is hard. I think I like it, but I'm not sure. Sometimes I finish a chapter and I feel like, &quot;Wow, that stream of consciences is just like how my brain thinks, except my brain uses smaller words, and uses less obscure allusions. In fact, I don't know if I think in allusions at all. Actually, now that I think about it, if I wasn't told by other people that there were allusions in this book, I wouldn't think there were allusions in this book. I wonder what I'm going to have for dinner. I'm going to have to cook for myself because mom and dad aren't home. Maybe I'll write my blog. Naw, I'm tired. How is James Joyce a real person? How did he give this book to someone and tell them 'Dude, don't worry. This book is awesome, people will read it forever,' and know it would get published? That would like me posting something on the internet about James Joyce and telling my mom, 'Don't worry, people will totally read this.'I like the book. It's a brain work out, but it's so different than, well, everything I've read. Screw it, I'm ordering pizza. What did I just read?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's just like that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went to Lawrence for the forty-ninth Great Midwest Trivia Contest. My team was &quot;Cardboard Dave's Soggie Wet Dream.&quot; I slept seven hours over the weekend. I made bacon ice cream. I saw a communist rally. I made a number of chodé puns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you who don't speak French, chodé translates to chode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paige is taking intro to micro-economics. I'm very proud of her. She made an econ joke. It caught me off gaurd when she did this. I mean, come on! I'm the one who shamelessly tells &quot;bad&quot; econ jokes. Here it is: she said, &quot;Our relationship is like a market: I demand and you supply.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don't get the joke, I recommend spending thousands of dollars and years of your life to go to college. If that doesn't sound like your thing or you already did that and still don't get the joke, &lt;a href=&quot;http://lmgtfy.com/?q=Supply+and+demand&amp;amp;l=1&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't google search chode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I saw &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline;&quot;&gt;Her&lt;/span&gt; last week. I really enjoyed it. There were several things I really liked about it. One thing I liked wasn't directly about what I got from the movie, rather, I like hearing all of the different reactions to the movie from other people. Most of the reactions are positive and focus on different things. To me, that's a sign of a good movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also really liked how well the movie portrayed relationships. It showed the quiet parts of a relationship; the silly little conversations that couples have can be random or even awkward, but they are still part of the relationship.  I really recommend you see the movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//--------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading. I feel that the way I write is very dependent on what I read. I read a Hemmingway short story last night and I'm having a hard time writing a sentence over five words. Hopefully you enjoyed it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email me at &lt;a href=&quot;kidman007@gmail.com&quot;&gt;kidman007@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; if you want to be added to the email list.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Greatest Hits Vol. XXIII</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/01/08/greatest-hits-vol-xxiii/"/>
   <updated>2014-01-08T03:54:10-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2014/01/08/greatest-hits-vol-xxiii</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’d like to start this post by saying Happy New Year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Happy. New. Year.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that we are done with that we can move onto more pressing topics, like politics, religion, fate, work, or happiness. Though we could talk about any of those vastly interesting and ever evolving debates, I’d like to talk about something else entirely: My Vacation. After that I’m probably going to make a drastic change of topic and talk about board games. If everything goes well – which it will (my blog my rules) - , &lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/7tT32gBsoa7REUNsazgXYW&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;I’ll probably &lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/7tT32gBsoa7REUNsazgXYW&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Leave a Link with music of awesome tunes for you to enjoy&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/i&gt;somewhere along the way. When I say the way, I mean my blog post. I’ll probably talk about books. I’ll probably talk about movies. Let’s find out. My blog, my rules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I left for vacation I took a strength finder assessment. It was a real assessment, not one of those random online tests that tells you which Hunger Games chapter best describes how you feel the morning after a night out. No, this test was legit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was pretty pleased with my results, as I think they were flattering and accurate. My top five strengths are: Positivity, Strategic, Ideation, Input, and Activator.  Perhaps this means that I am a positive, creative planner who makes sure to collect as much information before I gets the ball rolling. I can handle that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the flip-side, however, my “worst strength” was Achiever. So I guess this means that that I am a positive, creative planner who makes sure to collect as much information before I gets the ball rolling but is not that interested in working hard. Touché, Gallup strength finder, you got me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My vacation consisted of two parts: before Christmas and after New Year’s. Both – I must say – were excellent. I got to see Paige at length, which was nice, and I scored several sweet Christmas gifts, such as a brew your own beer kit. Awesome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The back half of my vacation was good as well. I went to Florida. I went to the beach. I sassed a fair amount. I ran on the beach once.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting back was an adventure. It involves my flight getting canceled, driving eight hours to Atlanta in order to catch a flight, and staying at the “#1 rated mid-range hotel chain in America,” The Drury Inn. After several mildly concerning events and my flight landing in Chicago, I was welcomed by negative eleven degree weather and a very talkative taxi driver from south Nigeria named Roger. He was very interesting and drove well. Thanks Roger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t actually want to talk about board games right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I read a few books over break. The first was &lt;i&gt;The &lt;/i&gt;Fall by Albert Camus. It was very interesting. The entire book was written as a one sided dialogue with a French man. I &lt;i&gt;highly&lt;/i&gt; recommend it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also read &lt;i&gt;Tuesdays with Morrie&lt;/i&gt;. I enjoyed the book. It was a little too, “I’m a hardworking guy who has ignored balance and peace in my life, but my old teacher/ mentor has clearly shown me of a better way to look at life and now I feel that I am a better person now,” for me at times. Despite that, it was a refreshing and good read. I think my co-worker - who has also read the book – put it best. He promised himself that he would only read the book while he was “on the can.” “On the Can” means sitting on the toilet while pooping or sitting on the toilet while waiting to poop. He only read the book while pooping. He said that given the circumstances that he read it in, “it wasn’t that bad,&quot; but it was definitely an &quot;‘on the can’ sort of book.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My co-worker is interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other news, I have decided to try to master speed reading. I took a speed reading class when I was younger and learned the “three finger underline method.” I didn’t keep up my training and lost my ability. Your brain can absorb information with your eyes faster than you can hear it, which means if you read each word in your head you can easily increase your reading speed without losing comprehension. Hopefully I won't get stuck on long books anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//--------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;American Hustle&lt;/i&gt; is the best movie I have seen in theaters since &lt;i&gt;All is Lost&lt;/i&gt;. The acting is fantastic. The movie reeks of style. The writing is sharp. Need I say more?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m really excited to see &lt;i&gt;Her&lt;/i&gt;. I wonder if I will like it more than &lt;i&gt;American Hustle.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me know what you think of the blog! If you want to be added to the distribution list or have any other questions, email me at: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:kidman007@gmail.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;kidman007@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Andrew Kraemer: Caring Zebra</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/12/16/andrew-kraemer-caring-zebra/"/>
   <updated>2013-12-16T01:48:42-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/12/16/andrew-kraemer-caring-zebra</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has been a while since my last post and quite a few things have happened. In an effort to not bore my beloved reader to death, I have provided a list of events and non-events that have happened to me recently:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-I made a playlist for this week. It is called “&lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/4fEl17cjufCms9XM4OHgCR&quot;&gt;Go Forward!&lt;/a&gt;” All of the songs are really good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-I left my keys in my trunk’s keyhole all day while I was at work. I couldn’t find them until eight p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Paige came down for an entire week. It was awesome. We watched shows, ate delicious food, and sassed each other constantly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-I made a ridiculous amount of Christmas cookies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really like this week’s playlist. The first song, “Divisionary (Do The Right Thing),” moved me when I first heard it. It is a straight forward sing along song. It is positive but with a sad tone. For some reason this song made me very nostalgic of playing with my band, And How!, because it sounds like a group of people who are messing around with their instruments and having a lot of fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second song, LCD Soundsystem’s “All My Friends,” made me think and be thankfull for all of my friends. It is also just great music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other tunes are just songs that I thought were really good. I hope you like the playlist as much as I do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a few people in my rotational program. We are all recent graduates from college and get along very well. One of them asked if I would be interested in starting a book club.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was hesitant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love books. But I barely have time to read the books that I am interested in. For instance, I have been slogging through Pillars of the Earth for about two months now (I only have about one-hundred pages left but I have not been able to find the book. I don't know how keen I am on finding and finishing it, though). I have a pile of books that is constantly growing next to my bedside table that I don’t read. Among others, my pile includes a Russian history book, a book about how cool classical music is, various fiction books, and an intimidating corporate finance text book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know I’ll get to these books sooner rather than later but a book club would do one of two things: I would have to put the books in my pile on hold for a long time, or I would have to try to trick the other readers into reading the random and eclectic books on my shelf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead, we are going to be doing an audiobook club. I’m very excited for this. It’s the best of both worlds. I’ll be able to read my own books and still be able to discuss books with other people like I did at school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any suggestions for good book club books, let me know. I’m thinking about recommending Hemmingway’s &lt;i&gt;The Sun Also Rises&lt;/i&gt; and a sci-fi book called &lt;i&gt;Snowcrash&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other night I was sitting in my car idling as I waited for the light to turn green. My mind was wondering. I was thinking about either a lot of things with no structure or nothing really at all. In other words, I was not paying much attention to anything at all. The light turned green. As my mind crept back into reality, I noticed a white Interceptor quickly crawl into the intersection and quickly accelerate into the darkness beyond. After driving for a minute I caught up to the cop car which had pulled over another car. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I thought to myself, “What an idiot. Why would he speed here? The cops always pull people over in this area. &lt;i&gt;He deserves what he gets&lt;/i&gt;” I continued pondering and changed my mind, “Regardless, that could have easily been me. That guy’s going to have to pay a ticket and everything now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For whatever reason, I continued to ponder about why I reacted in this way about a mundane traffic violation. My imagination took a leap. I thought the cop was like a lion or a cheetah, which was hiding in the tall Saharan grass waiting to pounce on its unsuspecting prey. The victim was like zebra. It was separated from the heard and was taken down by the predator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, this logic meant I was also a zebra in the heard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wondered if actual zebras had thoughts like this. Were they indifferent to the herd? Did they continue on with their lives – living as if the herd was only a group who provided protection? I was surprised that like the zebra I had no affection for the people around me. In my mind my fellow commuters are merely a heard of powered metal boxes that happens to be going in the same direction. We follow the same rules not because we want to but because it is convenient and safe for us on our journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a result of this mostly crazy logic I’ve decided to take extra care of being aware of the people around me. I don’t need to know who they are or what they do, but I want to make the effort to realize that the people around me are – in fact – people. Why?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps I just I want to be a caring zebra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Buttons: What's the Point?</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/11/26/buttons-whats-the-point/"/>
   <updated>2013-11-26T00:46:37-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/11/26/buttons-whats-the-point</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I'd like to start this post off by celebrating Paige again. Today is her birthday! If you see her celebrate the fact that he has been alive for twenty-three years. If you want, you can also celebrate the fact that she is a great person.&lt;br /&gt; -------//-------&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/0gwMS7h6XWoZN4pIVrTQJ9&quot;&gt;Here is this week's playlist&lt;/a&gt;. The theme is: music I like to listen to right now. We've got some soul, some rock, a little folk, and a weird sampling thing. &lt;br /&gt; -------//-------&lt;br /&gt; I've been reading the book &quot;Pillars of the Earth&quot; for what has seemed to be the last five years. I highly recommend reading Ken Follett's work, especially if you are on a beach or recovering from a Turkey coma. This book, however, I am more hesitant to recommend. I'm currently six-hundred pages in with four-hundred left to go. In my opinion, the characters are too one demential. The good guys are &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; good and the bad guys &lt;i&gt;such&lt;/i&gt; bastards. That is, the bad guys are not actual bastards, rather, they are just really big jerks. Perhaps I'll change my mind after another eon of reading and four-hundred pages.&lt;br /&gt; Speaking of bastards, I'm reading a book called &quot;Voltaire's Bastards.&quot; It critiques western societies' obsession with rationality. It is really interesting. Some parts I agree with and other parts I vehemently disagree with. I highly recommend this book if you are looking for an intellectual read, regardless of your opinions.&lt;br /&gt; -------//------- &lt;br /&gt; This past weekend I took the 'L' train down to Lincoln Park. I met with some good friends. We planned on making dinner, drinking delicious beer, going to a few hip bars, and thought going to a comedy club.&lt;br /&gt; I wore my new winter jacket with a scarf. My new jacket has buttons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Wearing a jacket with buttons has always seemed to be a silly thought to me. I remember seeing my friends my freshman year of college wearing jackets with buttons and scarves and thinking, &quot;Why are they doing that? That jacket doesn't look that warm and I bet the buttons fall off all of the time.&quot; Compared to the button, the zipper is clearly the more innovative, advanced, and, not to mention, secure fastening device. Why would anyone buy an inferior product for more money? I was utterly perplexed. All of this judgement of the buttoned jackets culminated to the decision that I would never buy a peacoat. It was a life of zippers for me. Efficiency over fashion! Truth over superficiality! Warmth over buttons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; But, four years later, here I was, standing in Lincoln Park wearing a jacket with buttons like a troglodyte.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I greeted my friend who, looking good as always, was also wearing a jacket with buttons. Standing next to us was a group of young 'Professional Looking' men and woman also wearing jackets which have buttons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; What's the big deal?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; This is about when I had a — mostly undramatic — crisis of conscience. Had I changed? Had my values changed? Am I now more of a mindless consumer following the herd of fashion-interested idiots? It seemed that something terrible had happened to the boy-man named Andrew Kraemer who for years wore a truly unfashionable zippered jacket that he bought out of necessity for twelve Euro.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Or, I thought to myself, is there possibly value in dressing this way?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; There are many ways in which people evaluate us. People can read or evaluate our work (or blogs). They can observe how we treat other people or how we participate in our communities. However, the easiest and quickest way to evaluate someone is to simply look at them. It's something we as humans can't help but do. We have evolved in such a way that we make judgements instantly and subconsciously about people based on the way they look. As we learn what certain people are like based upon their appearance, we have learned how to influence these immediate judgements with the way we dress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Perhaps part of me wants to look like a young professional, rather than that gangly guy who wore the ugly coat, even if it betrays my love of innovation. Of course, people take the idea of fashion and its value to extremes, but I think an equal number of people are doing themselves a disservice by ignoring any benefits of dressing well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; So there you have it, a reason to have in efficient buttons on your jacket. Spend away my friends. But I could keep going and explore the question more. There is the question of waste. Is there wasted material that goes into the buttons? Is there wasted effort on aesthetics rather than need? Why not invest in a single jacket that can withstand anything and it doesn't matter if it gets dirty? On the other hand is it waste if it creates value for both the person wearing the jacket and the person who makes and distributes the jacket. What if you had not bought that jacket and it impacted a whole ecosystem of friends who also got similar jackets and created wealth and a higher standard of living for the buttoned jacket maker?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I guess what I'm saying is that I have a hard time buying things. But, goddamnit, I like this jacket buttons and all. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Graduate, Leprosy, Courtney Barnet, and Chocolate-Dipped Science</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/11/11/167/"/>
   <updated>2013-11-11T03:28:16-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/11/11/167</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/7xWHg940OAvn0w78xe0CAo&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is a link to this post's playlist.  I found the first song on the playlist, &quot;Number 9,&quot; by Moon Hooch completely on accident. The band consists of two saxophone players and a drummer. Despite the bare-bones set up, Moon Hooch will get your booty moving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two of the songs in the playlist have the title &quot;Heart&quot; because why not. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Courtney Barnet's song &quot;Avant gardener&quot; is fantastic. Though I typically have trouble hearing and - as a result - caring about lyrics, I have found myself completely drawn in by Barnet's wordplay. I love how she delivers her lyrics as if they were a stream of consciousness but if you listen you can hear all of her incredibly and clever lines. Here is a taste:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;The paramedic thinks i’m clever cos i play guitar&lt;br /&gt;
I think she’s clever cos she stops people dying&lt;br /&gt;
Anaphylactic and super hypocondriactic&lt;br /&gt;
Should’ve stayed in bed today&lt;br /&gt;
I much prefer the mundane.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She reminds me a bit of the late Lou Reed of the Velvet Underground. Like Lou, Courtney delivers her lyrics dryly over a pretty simple chord structure. However, there is definitely some magic behind what she is doing. At least, that's what I think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------//------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This weekend I saw The Graduate for the first time. After the first fifteen minutes, I knew that this was going to be one of the best movies I've ever seen. I think that part of the reason I had this reaction is because I alway have mixed feelings before watching a movie that has been deemed a classic. I always want to enjoy classics because of the impact they have or had on art, but sometimes classics don't age very well. The Graduate pulled me in from the first scene. The camera keeps the viewer uncomfortably close to Dustin Hoffman's face as he awkwardly meets with friends of his family. I could go on, but I just recommend getting a big bowl of popcorn and watching the movie yourself if you haven't seen it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I try to be as open minded as possible and accept people for who they are, and, for the most part, I like to think I do pretty well. I try to reserve judgement until I have met someone, I and look at gossip with sceptisism. There are, however, some people that I don't think I could be open to in more than just a friendly way. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess what I'm trying to say is that I don't think I could date a leper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's not that I think that lepers are evil or that they aren't good people; rather, I just feel that there are a few too many barriers that would make the relationship work. First of all, leprosy is contagious and, well, I don't want leprosy. Second, even if it wasn't contagious, there are lots of things I couldn't do with my leper girlfriend. Say we were staying in (because we would always stay in because she would be a leper) and we agreed about something cool and exciting and highfived. What if I hit her hand clear off? Not only would it would be incredibly dangerous, but it would also be awkward for both of us. That is the sort of situation I just don't want to be in. And finally, I don't think I could date a leper because I am very happily dating and in love with Paige Koebele. She is wonderful, talented, beautiful, and (fingers crossed!) does not have leprosy. She makes me very happy. Our three year anniversary was on November sixth and I couldn't be happier. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So take that, single lepers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions, comments, or concerns, please email me at kidman007@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, you should let me know if you want to be on the distribution list of my blog. I can hook you up, yo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think that in future posts I am going to try to take more care with my writing. Lately, I have been typing as quickly as possible with minimal planning and editing in order to get a post out sooner rather than later. Part of the reason I'm doing this is to improve my writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AK&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Freud, Short Stories, and Giving Up on a Book</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/10/25/freud-short-stories-and-giving-up-on-a-book/"/>
   <updated>2013-10-25T01:54:58-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/10/25/freud-short-stories-and-giving-up-on-a-book</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I hope you are doing well because I feel great today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Here is the link to this post's playlist. It's entitled: &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/79813DUszgCe5CqWJGB97P&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline;&quot;&gt;Walking Around the House Naked at Two in the Afternoon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&quot; It's a pretty random collection of songs. I am particularly excited about &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline;&quot;&gt;Pretty Green&lt;/span&gt;, which is a new White Denim track. White Denim puts me in a mood that very few other bands can achieve. A feeling - no! A need to put my fist in the air and smile. (Editors note: Andrew Kraemer has been seen on multiple occasions raising his fist in the air with a determined, but triumphant, look on his face in his cubicle.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; -------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I picked up fifty-three volumes of the &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline;&quot;&gt;Britannica's Great Books of the Western World&lt;/span&gt; the other day from a rummage sale for thirty dollars. If you have an extra copy of volume fourty-one, &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline;&quot;&gt;The Decline and Fall of the Roman Empire (Part II)&lt;/span&gt;, let me know. It's the only volume out of the entire set I'm missing. I have mixed feelings about my purchase. I'm excited because there are a lot of really great books in there. On the other hand my reading list is already so long and I just put another fifty-three books on it. And when am I going to have the drive to go through some of these books? When am I going to sit down and tell myself, &quot;Andrew you're going to read hundreds of pages of Freud today.&quot;? At the very least, I have fifty-three fancy paperweights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; -------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I wrote a short story. It's not very good but that's ok. You can't expect your first time trying something to end up great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; It's about a guy who is being stalked by these two mysterious figures. The scene stops abruptly and continues. Many details change, such as location, charachters, and object at the reset of the scene. At the end you learn that every disjointed scene is just a guy trying to finish his dream but is interrupted by his alarm clock. I thought it was clever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; -------//-------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; In my opinion, it is always sad to give up on a book. I mention this because I gave up on a book yesterday. The book was Lucky Jim by Kingsley Amis. According to the back of the book, it is, &quot;Regarded by many as the finest, and funniest, comic novel of the twentieth century.&quot; I respectfully disagree and call bullshit on that comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I really wanted to enjoy the story. But after 100 pages I found myself not caring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; When is it ok to give up on a book? Let's ask ourselves a few questions before we abandon the book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 1. Did you lose your bookmark?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; This is not a valid excusue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 2. Are the characters too stupid for you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Sometimes the characters in a novel make repeated poor decisisons. Sometimes the characters are so foolish that it breaks your willing suspense of disbelief. If you have been dealing with stupid charachters, close that book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 3. Is the book not at all what you expected in a bad way?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Being surprised by a good book is a great feeling. For instance, I read &quot;The Passage&quot; with absolutely no background other than a friend telling me, &quot;Dude, I read this 1000 page book in like a day. It was awesome.&quot; With no background other than that it was probably a horror story (&quot;Steven King called 'The Passage' a dazzling world&quot; was on the cover).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; This is not always the case. It took me a long time to read &quot;Lord of the Rings&quot; because I expected an action novel rather than an adventure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Give books that do this to you a chance - I'd say give it 100-150 pages. If the book still isn't clicking. Throw it out the window and dig it out of your garden a year from now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 4. Are you incredibly bored?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; There's a chance you are reading a book that is too easy for you. More likely, however, the book is above your reading level, which is a shame because the book is right up your alley but you just can't appreciate it because of your brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 5. Are you in a substantial amount of emotional or physical pain?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I understand that a book can play with your emotions and this can cause some emotional pain. But this pain is the emotional and psychological roller-coaster we want from a book. I'm talking about bad pain. I'm talking about that pain you get when you are reading Stephen Hawking's &quot;A Brief History of Time&quot; expecting a fun and easy science read. That, my friends, is the stinging pain of surprise and disaointment. If you are experiencing this, I encourage you to put down the book and walk to the nearest library and go to the children's section and read &quot;Nate the Great&quot; until you feel better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; --------//--------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Email me at Kidman007@gmail.com if you want to be put on the email list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I have a lot of things I want to write but not enough time! I start an online finance course on Monday. Despite this, I will continue to post as much as I can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I think I'm going to sit down and read hundreds of pages of Freud now.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Some Words on Writing</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/10/08/some-words-on-writing/"/>
   <updated>2013-10-08T01:37:59-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/10/08/some-words-on-writing</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hi, how are you? I hope you are having a good [insert time of day]. I'm doing pretty well [insert your name]. Thanks for asking. I encourage you to read &quot;I'm the Knife You're the Knife&quot; from this week's issue of the New Yorker. It's the best short story I have read in some time. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------//---------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This [insert time period until next post]'s playlist. &lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/30UUHS0a8f6kMgpCGvLNAH&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is the link. I hope you like it. I like it because it has good music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------//--------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;It has only been in the last couple of years that I started to enjoy writing.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;This enjoyment has manifested itself in a few ways. One of the more obvious ways I write for enjoyment is in a small black jouranal I almost always keep in my pocket. I like doing this for two reasons. First, I like to think that I'm an active person, so it makes sense for me to always have a journal with me, rather than keep it untouched in some well lit room with a comfy chair, calligraphy pens, books on all of the walls, classical music lightly - but not too loudly - playing in the background, and a large wooden desk that smells of rich mahogany. The second reason I keep the small notebook is because it is a real pain in the ass to carry around and if I didn't write in it I would feel like an idiot.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Oh, and I also write a blog.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;It took me a long time to like writing because for so long I thought I was bad at writing. I have a clear memory of being in kindergarten and having to write in a journal. I remember all of the other kids writing quickly and then going and playing with toys, but I was stuck sitting for what felt like hours with my teacher, Mrs. Turner. I trying to write, &quot;I like to eat pizza.&quot; It was hell. In high school I thought my writing was fine, not exceptional, but fine. It was in College when I began to feel self conscience about my writing. Many Lawrentians claim that they really begin to learn how to write during Lawrence's trademark &quot;Freshman Studies&quot; courses. I, on the other hand, watched Bill and Ted's Excellent Journey in my class and learned nothing (the professor no longer teaches at Lawrence). It was when I started to actually care about learning when I began to think I was a bad writer.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;I would spend hours and hours writing a single paragraph. I would be dissatisfied with the structure or a small grammatical element, try to correct it, then be dissatisfied with the correction, try to correct it again, realize the flow did not work, and then get frustrated and rewrite everything all over again. &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;I eventually came to terms with myself and decided that though I can make grammer mistakes and I don't always say things exactly how I want to say them, I can write well enough to enjoy it. Writing the blog has been really good for me because I can play with words and get better, or I can just type as fast as I can to share some of my goofy thoughts.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; ---------//---------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email me at Kidman007@gmail.com if you want to be put on the email list!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>My most random hobby</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/09/25/my-most-random-hobby/"/>
   <updated>2013-09-25T03:06:52-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/09/25/my-most-random-hobby</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Listen &lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/4p07Se7IJWR7W681322Eqn&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for the playlist made for this week. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a lot of interests and a lot of hobbies. In fact, I think that there are not enough hours in the day to give all of my hobbies the proper attention they deserve. The main reason I don't have enough time is because of this whole &quot;working&quot; thing. I usually walk into the mighty Catamaran building at 8:30 a.m. and leave anywhere from 5:30-7:30 p.m. depending on the day (this week had two 7:30 leaving days - oofta). The other main obstacle is my commute, which is usually an hour long each way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though I don't have a terrible commute, I made a decision early on that I did not want to spend two hours of my day listening to music and slamming my forehead against the steering-wheel due to a traffic induced rage. As a result, I now actually really enjoy my commute. In the morning I listen to music for a while - a whole album if I'm in the mood - or listen to a podcast. I used to listen to books on tape on my way home, but Anna Karinina eventually ruined that for me. Now I have found a new activity for my ride home: I'm learning Mandarin Chinese. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What? How? Chinese you say?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being the young professional that I am, I have become interested in self improvement and time management tips and techniques. To pursue that interest I picked up the book The Power of Habit by Charles Duhigg. The book itself was not that good. It was a typical blockbuster nonfiction book. It has a few really good ideas and A LOT of fluff. I learned from the book that you can do anything if you make it a habit. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After I finished the book, I blinked, opened my notebook and wrote &quot;I am going to learn Chinese.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The decision surprised me. First off, I have always hated languages - even English. When I was younger, I used to say, &quot;I don't use grammar because I write n' speak American,&quot; and I meant it.&lt;br /&gt; Despite my original 'hesitation' towards learning languages, I went out and stole Pimslur Chinese on the internet and started my Ni Haos and Wo Hoi Shwa Yin One Mas (I have no idea how to write anything with Chinese characters or proper phonetics, so bear with me). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far learning has been difficult but a lot of fun. I try to do a lesson once a day even if I had a long day and just want to listen to an NPR report on rabies, babies, or scabies. It's weird. When I try a lesson for the first time I get annihilated and it sucks. However, after I try the lesson again a second time, the language begins to flow a little. I hope sometime soon I can try to find a way to apply what I have learned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------//-----------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided recently that I am going to learn python, a programming language. Unfortunately, I will need to figure out where this will fall in my list of priorities. Is it above Chinese? Above work? Below working out? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, the choices I must make in my difficult life. Sigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------------//-----------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No editing was done for this post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leave me a message at kidman007@gmail.com if you want to be on the email list!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The End of Summer, or: Why Milk is at the Back of the Grocery Store</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/09/12/the-end-of-summer-or-why-milk-is-at-the-back-of-the-grocery-store/"/>
   <updated>2013-09-12T04:06:30-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/09/12/the-end-of-summer-or-why-milk-is-at-the-back-of-the-grocery-store</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I hear that it has been hot outside but I wouldn't know; I spend the majority of the time the sun is out in an air conditioned cubicle. Despite this alleged heat wave, the transition from summer to PSLS (Pumpkin Spice Latte season)  - also known as fall - has begun. In celebration of the change of seasons, I have created a spottily playlist that is has all of the characteristics of a Pumpkin Spice Latte: sweet, surprising, and most likely disappointing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/1P1kPIyWyo4JIYLZ5KxWuG&quot;&gt;End of Summer Playlist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The playlist starts out with one of my new favorite songs by King Khan entitled &quot;Born to Die.&quot; The song is almost as crazy as the story of the band. For example, after a mental break down, the lead singer of the band, Ahmad Khan, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.spin.com/articles/king-khan-shrines-idle-no-more-merge-records-album-stream/&quot;&gt; joined an all female group of Korean Nuns&lt;/a&gt; along with other odd life decisions in order to cope with his depression before releasing this awesome LP. Later in the playlist is a band called &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.radiolab.org/blogs/radiolab-blog/2013/aug/29/dawn-midi/&quot;&gt;Dawn of Midi&lt;/a&gt;. I encourage you to listen to their newest album, Dysnomia, in full. The entire album is improvised but somehow the band - a piano, bass, and drums - sounds sounds like a computer. It's very cool. The final song is a collaboration between Moby and Wayne Coyne. It sounds a little &quot;Hey Jude&quot;ish, but that's ok because I love &quot;Hey Jude.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The playlist is eclectic; but hey, I think it's better than a PSL.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------------//--------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why is Milk kept in the back of the grocery store? Think of an answer now and we will explore some answers in a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I have mentioned in previous posts, I listen to a few economics podcast in order to keep my economic intuition sharp. Econ Talk, my favorite economics podcast, is moderated professor Russ Roberts of Stanford University. The talks are always interesting, but this week's podcast was so engaging I felt that I needed to share it, despite its mundane title, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.econtalk.org/archives/2013/09/munger_on_milk.html&quot;&gt;Munger on Milk&lt;/a&gt;. In this podcast, Roberts posts the question, &quot;Why is Milk in the back of the Grocery Store?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The explanation that came to my mind was milk is in the back of the store in order to force consumers to walk through the whole store and, as a result, increases amount of goods the customer sees and buys. It makes sense right? A grocery store is a firm. Firms are focused on maximizing profits. Because the margins on food are so slim a store tries to get the customer to buy as many things as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately for me and my &quot;sharp economic intuition,&quot; Roberts destroys my theory. He counters with questions such as, why do store owners clean the floors? Why do they hire cheerful people at the checkout line? The store could save money by cutting these services out and thus make more money. However, thanks to competition, grocery stores have to compete with other grocery stores and have to provide good service. If the store tried to screw over the customer as much as possible, the customer would go to a different store. Competition forces the stores to place things that they are as convenient as possible. Stores that fail to adapt would be abandoned for better organized stores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Besides, milk is in the back of the store because it is cheaper to stock it in the back for a number of reasons that I won't explain here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roberts goes further to encourage people to avoid immediately assuming a firm is out to get them. He concedes that yes, sometimes you are getting screwed over; but, he argues,&lt;i&gt; if you are open to the possibility that firms are trying to serve you in their interest, you will be able to see explanations that you would have otherwise missed.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think that this is AWESOME!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This goes with my whole philosophy of everything. If you take a second to assume the negative case of something, you are more likely to be able to discover new answers. The answers may not be correct, but at least you have a more thorough understanding of the problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------------//-------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully that was in English. Let me know if there are any glaring errors that bother you and I will fix them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me know if you want me to be on an email list by emailing me at kidman007@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andrew&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. My learning of Chinese has been going well.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Why a young professional near Chicago lives at home: a cost benefit analysis</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/09/05/why-a-young-professional-near-chicago-lives-at-home-a-cost-benefit-analysis/"/>
   <updated>2013-09-05T03:02:31-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/09/05/why-a-young-professional-near-chicago-lives-at-home-a-cost-benefit-analysis</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I'd like to start by apologizing for the unforgivable tardiness of this post. I've gotten busier with work - which I realize is not an excuse - and I have had a blog post that I have wanted to write but haven't put the effort into fully explore the idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite my apparent busyness, I have been having a great time as of late. I have had back to back great weekends. One weekend was in Eagle River, Wisconsin, which included a brief but emotionally necessary stop in Steven's Point. Many of my good friends met and we had a wonderfully manly weekend on a lake. This most recent weekend I was in St. Paul, Minnesota; where I got to see a plethora of wonderful cousins and my wonderful girlfriend, Paige. I went to the state fair and ate my weight and the some of various fried skewered &quot;foods&quot; and went home with a smile on my face despite the painful sensation of my gut being dragged on the concrete and occasionally getting stepped on by the &quot;ooooh-I-know-right?&quot;ing locals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------//-------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope we don't bomb Syria. I'm a bit of a pacifist. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------//-------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Listen to Dawn of Midi. It's some of the best music I've heard all summer. It's jazz musicians discovered electronic music and play acoustic. Great stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------//-------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Nobel prize winner Ronald Coase died at the age of 102. I liked him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------//-------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently I've been thinking about the fact that I live at home rather than the exciting and mysterious city of Chicago. I know that I will be moving away from home eventually, but the question is when will this be happening. In order to better understand my situation, I decided to do a quick cost benefit analysis - ya know, for kicks. In this analysis I will value different parts of the analysis with &quot;Kraemer Republic Action Points,&quot; which will be referred to as KRAP. Though the points will not be tied to dollars in any way shape or form, I can tell you I give about 300 KRAPs a month to pay my car loan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cons of living at home:&lt;br /&gt;
You have to tell people you are living at home:&lt;br /&gt;
Now this might not sound like a big deal but, I must say, it is weird telling people that you are living at home even though you have a job and could technically afford your own apartment. People will reenforce your decision and act be excited when you tell them you are living at home. However, these same people's faces will light up when they hear that you are living down town. They lean in closer and ask what neighborhood your are in, what are your cross streets and what festival you went to that weekend. Saying you live at home is boring. I'd say I give about 150 KRAPs a month about that.&lt;br /&gt;
You aren't in the city:&lt;br /&gt;
Young, goodlooking people like myself live in the city. I like young people and I like fun things. For instance, this weekend there is a Guinness and Oyster festival. I'd say I give about 300 KRAPs a month to live in the city.&lt;br /&gt;
You have a big close (and frustrating family:&lt;br /&gt;
My family is great but sometimes I just want a little time to myself. One time I went into my room to get away for a little bit after a long day at work and not one, not two, but three of my family members burst into my room unannounced. This can be draining. I'd say I give about 237 KRAPs about that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know that I've been talking a lot of KRAP about living at home, but there are definitely some positives as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pros:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No rent/ other cost savings&lt;br /&gt;
I save a ton of KRAP by living at home. Rent in downtown Chicago would like be dumping all of my KRAP down the toilet. I'm probably saving 600 KRAPs per month on rent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Family:&lt;br /&gt;
Though I love to complain about my family, I must say - I really like being with them. It's fun to watch tv shows with my brother Daniel. I like driving my sister Diane to school in the morning. Life is good at home. I give a lot of crap about my family about 340 KRAPs!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that I'm a financial analysis I know math. With my math skill I figure that I'm saving 253 KRAPs per month living at home. Ain't that nifty. If, however, I develop an acute distaste for my family or I give less KRAPs about money I'll move out. Despite this, I get the feeling that an external something will push me towards the big city. I don't know what that something is, but until then ill be chilling with my brother.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------//-------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want me to email you when I put up a post send me an email at kidman007@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lub,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andrew&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Sleepiness, statistics, buildings and books - for breakfast!</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/08/16/sleepiness-statistics-buildings-and-books-for-breakfast/"/>
   <updated>2013-08-16T02:28:34-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/08/16/sleepiness-statistics-buildings-and-books-for-breakfast</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have a lot of random things I would like to explore and/or remark about, so please bare with me on this post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First off, &lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/user/kidman007/playlist/6VnPRSlK3uvAoDqnbw65wt&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; is a Spotify playlist of cool &lt;b&gt;tunes&lt;/b&gt; I have been rocking out to. Props to my cousin Tommy for recommending a few of these songs. Tommy is a DJ and you should check out the songs he has made &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/hot-mischief&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; on his sound cl&lt;b&gt;oud&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second, I annihilated my tongue on a cup of coffee on Monday and today - Thursday - it still hurts. I probably deserve it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monday I was in an especially great mood. In fact, I felt like &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline;&quot;&gt;this&lt;/span&gt; the entire day (1).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of the reason I feel this way is because my company moved to a really cool new building in Schaumburg. It has modern design things everywhere. I have my own cube, which I have already pinned on my wall a sheet of excel hotkeys and a picture of my own face. We have a cafeteria that reminds me of Bon Appetite - the good food service my school used - except even better! I also get to sit next to my team which is awesome. Though we work hard for most of the day, we do have our bursts of goofiness. These goofy moments include, but are not limited to, shirtless Bon Jovi themed birthday cards (don't ask and no, it was not my idea), launching notes to each other with rubber bands above the cube walls, and a mini game of bags. Needless to say, the transition from my crappy old building to this modern Google-wannabe building is awesome.&lt;br /&gt;
--&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wondered what it would be like to have statistics on your entire life? I think about it all of the time. Thoughts such as, &quot;how many cups of coffee have a drank in my life?&quot;, &quot;what days do I drink the most cups of coffee on average?&quot;, or &quot;How many hours have I actually been using my brain today?&quot; I feel like it would be so cool to know everything about myself, because - lets be honest - we typically don't know ourselves as well as we think we do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll probably write about this more at some point, but for now just let that thought bounce around your head&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm currently reading the fantasy novel &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline;&quot;&gt;Sabriel&lt;/span&gt;. I’m enjoying the story though I’m not sure I would recommend it. The story is interesting enough but it is definitely a book for a younger audience. The prose is often awkward and I have a hard time connecting with the characters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After I finish this book - which I am hoping to do tonight – I will begin the hard-boiled crime thriller &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline;&quot;&gt;Double Indemnity&lt;/span&gt;. It looks like a really fun, short, and classic read. The book was recommended to me by Prof. Podair. I have a feeling he has good taste in crime thrillers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm so sleepy. I hope the post was in English.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------//---------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1) That is, I felt really good like the song - not like the video. If I felt like the video I feel like I would be implying that I was totally warped on acid, which I certainly was not.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Donuts and Innovation</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/08/10/donuts-and-innovation/"/>
   <updated>2013-08-10T15:23:20-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/08/10/donuts-and-innovation</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I love innovation. I love change. Innovation and change lead to improvement in all sorts of things. I like that. To me, &lt;a href=&quot;http://images.search.yahoo.com/images/view;_ylt=A0PDoKnTWQZSJRoACKyjzbkF;_ylu=X3oDMTF1b2M2ZzQ4BHNlYwNmcC1leHAEc2xrA2V4cARvaWQDOWMwZTYzZjRjZmQ1MzhkZmVkYTdhMzFhMWE4YzI1Y2EEZ3BvcwM4?back=http%3A%2F%2Fsearch.yahoo.com%2Fsearch%3Fei%3DUTF-8%26p%3Dschumpeter%26type%3D571829%26fr%3Dspigot-adr-ffmac&amp;amp;w=305&amp;amp;h=400&amp;amp;imgurl=hightechhistory.files.wordpress.com%2F2011%2F01%2Fschumpeter1.jpg&amp;amp;rurl=http%3A%2F%2Fhightechhistory.com%2Ftag%2Fj-p-morgan%2F&amp;amp;size=19.3KB&amp;amp;name=Joseph+Alois+%3Cb%3ESchumpeter%3C%2Fb%3E&amp;amp;p=schumpeter&amp;amp;oid=9c0e63f4cfd538dfeda7a31a1a8c25ca&amp;amp;fr2=&amp;amp;fr=&amp;amp;tt=Joseph+Alois+%3Cb%3ESchumpeter%3C%2Fb%3E&amp;amp;b=0&amp;amp;ni=160&amp;amp;no=8&amp;amp;ts=&amp;amp;tab=organic&amp;amp;sigr=11aqbraij&amp;amp;sigb=12kk739jj&amp;amp;sigi=11rk3hlds&amp;amp;.crumb=E9o3.hs/eoh&amp;amp;&quot;&gt;Joseph Schumpeter&lt;/a&gt; - an innovation focused economist - is more than a hero to me; he is a friend. Innovation is constant and competitive and beautiful and I love that. But today at work I experienced what it is like to fail and be disappointed when you try something new.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The day began like most other days. I cruised to work listening to podcasts and trying - futilely - to learn Chinese. Because I had a long and productive week in the office and that it is the last day in our current building, I figured that I would a pretty easy day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I could not have been more wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The email came in at 9:16 from Christina. It was entitled 'Donuts.' I perked up and rose from my seat. The prospect of a sugary treat made my mouth water. I followed my nose to the tray of donuts. There were donuts of all types. I reached my hand out towards my favorite kind of donut, strawberry frosting. Then, I stopped myself and thought, &quot;What would Schumpeter do? Why don't I try innovating my donut eating habits?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My eyes drifted over the trans-fat-filled sugary delights and I saw a beautiful donut. It had white frosting, some mysterious crunchy flair on the top, and it was filled with a cream that I could not see.  I heard it calling to me so quickly grabbed it and ran back to my desk with a cup of coffee. The first bite was delicious. I love the way that cream filled donuts feel when you get a bite without cream. Then I took another bite and despair flowed through my entire body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was filled with lemon cream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's not that I don't like lemons. It was just not what I was looking for; especially when compared to the serene beauty of the strawberry frosting donut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The moral of the story, I guess, is that even though trying new things can lead to beautiful innovations and grand new experiences it is also risky and may lead to failure or dissapointment. It is important to note, however, that these disappointments and failures are good for us. We learn more about what doesn't work and and the nice things about we know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep failing (you just might learn something).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;—————————–//—————————–&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>And How!</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/08/07/and-how/"/>
   <updated>2013-08-07T04:03:07-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/08/07/and-how</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;I just remember sitting in my attic with an old record player, listening to And How! for hours on end and thinking to myself, &quot;Why can't I sound like that?&quot; -Thom Yorke&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since the fall of 2009 the world famous band, And How!, has certianly changed the landscape of music. It all started when Jared Marchant, who is now the band's manager, discovered the band on a Friday night in Ormsby Hall at Lawrence University during drunken jam session. He recalled how he felt when he first experienced And How!, &quot;When I walked in to the room I heard the music and immediately felt like my ears were hit simultaneously by a bizarre - but perfect - combination of roses and dynamite.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The band steadily grew more popular thanks to Mr. Marchant. The band released their hit &quot;Krunk Punk&quot; which immediately dominated the radio waves on classic rock stations and influenced many young artists, such as Jimi Hendrix:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&quot;The Tower&quot; is cool. I can't help but think that the Grateful Dead's Dark Star was somehow influenced by it. All the elements are there. But I suppose that would be somewhat anachronistic, wouldn't it? -Jimi Hendrix&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since then the band has released seventy-two albums and shows no signs of slowing down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The band's latest album, &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline;&quot;&gt;Let It Be&lt;/span&gt;, includes many new ground breaking jams. &quot;Krunktry&quot; is an example of the going back to their southern country roots and their love of america, peace, freedom, bald eagles, openness, and love. It also has a very strong themes of xenophobia and a strong repulsion of communism - especially Chinese communism. Near the end of the star spangled epic, Tony Darling, the band's drummer and Creed-style vocalist, begs the listener to consider what it means to truly be an American by asking, &quot;do you think you get get a DUI on a stallion?&quot; Some call this lyricism brilliant. I disagree. I call it art.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matt Gunby (Guitar) is confident that their new album will do well as he said in an interview with Rolling Stone, &quot;I think the new album will do well.&quot; Tony Darling, on the other hand, stated, &quot;I don't get why we added 'Morning Wouldn't' to the album. It ruins the the whole aesthetic of the album and, lets face it, anyone who buys the album simply will not be maximizing their utility. Without 'Morning Wouldn't,' I would say that it's our best album since &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline;&quot;&gt;Ninth Symphony? What the Fugue in G minor is Wrong With You?&lt;/span&gt;. Seriously, &amp;amp;%$# that song.&quot; Karl Mayer (Saxophone) was unable to make as he is currently missing, though he was last seen in the Himalayas barefoot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andrew Kraemer (bass) declined to comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;—————————–//—————————–&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>iBreakup</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/08/01/breakup/"/>
   <updated>2013-08-01T04:57:04-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/08/01/breakup</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have had an iPhone 4 since January 2011. This phone has been very good to me. We have worked together in order to communicate with other people. I press its screen and it makes letters and messages that appear that I send to both my friends and my enemies. I like that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We, that is my iPhone and I, have been on many adventures together. We have gone on many long walks and road trips together. I usually - but not always - decide where we go. Everything was perfect with our relationship until the accident happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I say that it is not the phone's fault but mine that our relationship has gone south, I really do mean it. There was that party when I was focusing on my friends and I left the iPhone there and, well, it got stepped on repeatedly. The screen is cracked the the battery life is short, but these are just physical things. The real problem is much deeper. I'm just ready to move on. Since then it was obvious that I would get a new phone. The only question is how long we would be able to put up with each others flaws.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, however, due to being on my family plan and the 'aggressive' manner my family uses phones, use the only upgrade available would be another iPhone 4. An upgrade from an iPhone 4 to an iPhone 4 isn't really an upgrade. I realize that this is certainly a first world problem, so I will continue with this (damaged but functional) awesome futuristic mini-computer-phone and keep my mouth shut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;                                    -----------------------------//-----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Tequila and Müstaché Memoirs, or My Saturday at Pitchfork Music Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/07/25/the-tequila-and-mustache-memoirs-or-my-saturday-at-pitchfork-music-festival/"/>
   <updated>2013-07-25T04:36:36-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/07/25/the-tequila-and-mustache-memoirs-or-my-saturday-at-pitchfork-music-festival</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div&gt;If you know me well, you would know that I have been to a fair amount of music festivals. Every festival has its own unique flavor. Some are free and some you have to pay for. Each festival has its own unique crowd. For instance, Warped Tour is filled with people who look like they ride skate boards; I don’t know why, they just do.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;This year I went to Pitchfork music festival. This was my second time going so I knew what to expect. The acts are not as big as those at Lollapalooza; nor are there as many people. One you arrive, however, you are immediately exposed to a sea of people sporting trendy sunglasses, tribal tattoos, jean shorts (commonly referred to as “jorts”), mustaches, and craft beer. It is at Pitchfork where this crowd of ironic creative types go to worship their independent music gods.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;So naturally I came running to the festival this year.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;My cohorts and I arrived at the festival after a nasty traffic ridden drive from Wilmette. Proudly wearing festival battle gear, which includes: my white hat with a bold green “W”, my chuck tailors, high socks, (slightly) short shorts, Ray Bans, and my ‘And How!’ shirt (And How! is so underground), we passed through the entrance of the park. Getting in was a suspiciously stress-free experience considering that I had a freezer bag full of tequila stuffed down my pants. We waded through a sea of culturally relevant shops that had records of bands that I have probably heard of and fairtrade-organic-handmade-vegan leather items. We then purchased our first round of craft beer, cider, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cookingchanneltv.com/recipes/chuck-hughes/tequila-lemonade.html&quot;&gt;lemonade for the tequila&lt;/a&gt; – of course – and made our way to the Green Stage. Here we waited for our first band of the day, the Savages.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Savages was one of the few bands that I was familiar with that was playing that day and certainly the one I was most excited to see. The band consists of four bad-ass women. They released their first album, Silence Yourself, early this year and it is reminiscent of the post-punk bands of the late 70’s and 80’s, such as Joy Division, Gang of Four, and Wedding Present. Though the band is young, they performed with the confidence and control of a band that has been touring for years. I rocked out for the entire set. You could hear the bass crisply dancing along with the rock solid drums. The lead singer was engaging and mysterious and the guitar dissonantly  meandered. It was awesome. While listening to the songs I was quite familiar with I was embarrassingly exposed to what I will call a &quot;Punk Rock Epiphany.&quot; This happens when you are trying to identify a punk rock song and can't. This is because every punk rock song sounds pretty much the same. Though the performance was fantastic, I couldn't help but wish that the show was inside. I wanted a dark crowded space to mosh in and feel gloomy. In addition the pale women of the Savages looked like they were getting sun-burnt during their brief stint in the sun. Despite the slight wishes for the show to be indoors, the experience was great on all accounts and it was a fantastic way to begin the festival. If you want to get a good taste of the band I recommend checking out my favorite song by them, &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kim-REn8ecg&quot;&gt;She Will&lt;/a&gt;.&quot;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;As the next was playing at the blue stage not far in the distance, the Swans - which is simply not a band I enjoy, we refueled on the finest dining Union Park had to offer. We happily gorged ourselves on Chubbie’s hotdogs, cheese fries, and a bag of bacon. We also took this time to continue sampling more craft beers and creative lemonade-tequila concoctions. There was much rejoicing.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;After the successful binge, we went back to the Green Stage and met up with many of my family members who arrived late and watched the next band, The Breeders, performed their most famous album, ‘Last Splash,’ in its entirety. Kim Deal, the lead singer of the band, is the former bassist of the Pixies. Despite being twenty years older than when she was when she recorded the album, you could tell that she still knew how to rock out and have good time. It was interesting to see the band make all of the different sounds that appear on the album. For instance, to achieve the odd dissonant voice in the song &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fxvkI9MTQw4&quot;&gt;Cannonball&lt;/a&gt;&quot; Kim shouted into a megaphone, which is pretty punk rock. After playing the album, the band played a few more of their hits thanked the crowed and left the stage.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Our jolly band surged forward after the Breeders ended in order to get a good position for the Headliner that night, Bele and Sebastian. Before the Scottish band took the stage, Paige and I were given the task of getting more select craft beers from the beverage tent. We also desperately needed more lemonade for the tequila. Getting the beverages was easy; bringing six cups back with only two people was quite a bit more difficult. Perhaps it was being in the sun all day, perhaps it was because she has tiny hands, or maybe it was just the ethanol, regardless of what was going on, Paige failed to maintain control of the three cups of beer. She successfully spilled half a glass of Goose Island Green Line all over herself as she attempted to regain control and sit on the ground. As a result, I became in charge of transporting 50 ounces of beverages through a crowd.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Surprisingly, the experience of wading through the crowd of people was far more positive than I anticipated. This is because fans of Belle and Sebastian are like the music of Belle and Sebastian, that is, very nice. I parted the sea of people witha few smiles and thank you’s - kinda like Moses (but not really). In fact, when my Tequila concoction began to fall out of my arm, people quickly rushed to my aid and let me through. If I was to describe my feelings at this point in three words, it would be this: I love hippies.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Belle and Sebastian put on a fantastic show from start to finish. The band began with a fun instrumental track which I later learned was entitled “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xa9_BQdfo50&quot;&gt;Judy is a Dickslap&lt;/a&gt;.” My mother and father bobbed their heads to this song regardless. Some things just should not be explained. The positive energy of the evening would be impossible to extinguish. About half way through the show there was a pleasant drizzle that complimented the pleasantness of this Scottish band. Later, near the end of the show, the band invited about twenty people from the crowd on stage. One woman, a former audience member (now dancer), was dancing with only a bra on. Rather than looking with interest or excitement, the male lead singer simply asked the woman, &quot;Where is you shirt?&quot; and continued singing as if he had not just seen a mostly naked person. I wonder what was going through her mind at that point. I bet it was something along the lines of, &quot;Scottish people have funny accents.&quot;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;After closing to a singalong of &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zeVJlLxGsmo&quot;&gt;Boy With the Arab Strap&lt;/a&gt;,&quot; we left the festival wet, giddy, and thoroughly exhausted. We also had no more tequila. The festival was a great experience and I already can't wait for next year.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How to Write Your First Blog Post</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/07/19/how-to-write-your-first-blog-post/"/>
   <updated>2013-07-19T21:10:35-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/07/19/how-to-write-your-first-blog-post</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step One: Introduce Yourself (feel free to skip)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, I'm Andrew Kraemer. I live in Wilmette Illinois. I recently graduated from Lawrence University where I learned (I think) to think. I recently began working for a pharmacy benefit management company called Catamaran as a financial analyst. Don't let my employment fool you - I'm a pretty goofy person. I like to think that I am pretty good at seeing the humor of everyday life. I am remarkably tall. I am redheaded and freckled. I'm also currently dating a wonderful girl named Paige. I have a lot of interests; probably too many for my own good. I love reading. I try to read everything from daily news to Ancient Greek history (translated of course). I'd write more about books now but I  have an agenda to get through. I like coffee a lot. I'd write more about this as well; I feel like I could just do a post on coffee. I have recently begun to meditate. I love music of many different types. I've recently been getting into board games, which I believe is representative of my dark and extensive nerdy side. Something I've come to learn about myself recently as well is that I hate generalizations. If you are planning on say something, say it right!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And yeah... I think that covers everything about me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Two: Explain Why You are Writing a Blog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Earlier today I was showering and I had a flood of ideas. Here is a small sample of thoughts: &quot;I wish I had a nemesis.&quot;, &quot;Do I prefer chaos or order?&quot;, &quot;How did I not foresee the twist in that book?&quot; The thoughts exploded relentlessly in my mind. I struggled to think of one thing at a time or just think about normal person things. As the cascade of ideas continued to pop in my head I decided that it might be a good idea for me to write these thoughts down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also want a way to share my life with people in my own way. I have many friends that I may not see for a long time now that I have graduated, so I figured it might not be bad idea to share these written thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to my liberal arts degree I was able to solve both of these problems with one solution: write a blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3: Write a Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;I fully intend on stealing a lot of ideas and information. I'll try to link things but I won't try too hard. Remember, this is a blog we are talking about! It's supposed to be recreational!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll try to write once a week. I'll try to put some real thought and some real effort into each post. The writing may be sporadic, however. Like camels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I feel passionate about something I may be vulgar about it. I'm sorry if it offends you, goddamnit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Step: Write Something Funny or Interesting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll leave you (my many fans) with this funny thought:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Babies are incredibly stupid. No amount of love or cuteness can make this statement untrue. Let's dive a little deeper and I'll tell you why I think this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First off, babies are completely helpless creatures. If I was to walk into a forest and left the baby out of earshot it would certainly be eaten or die of starvation within a very short amount of time. They wouldn't be able to get to safety because are physically incapable of walking because they are too weak. In fact, many babies can't even support their own (mostly) useless heads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Babies can barely think. They are so stupid that if they see a ball and then if the ball is covered by a sheet, in the babies mind, &lt;em&gt;the ball ceases to exist&lt;/em&gt;. That is stupidity that I can not relate to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though babies are quite dumb, I must hand it to them, they do eventually become some pretty smart and capable people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you enjoyed my first post! I'll post more soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
